<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>PulseGeek</title>
  <id>https://pulsegeek.com/atom.xml</id>
  <updated>2025-11-18T16:16:00Z</updated>
  <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://pulsegeek.com" />
  <author>
    <name>PulseGeek</name>
  </author>
  <subtitle>Tech news, gaming, and geek culture in one pulse</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>Confusion Matrix for Security Classifiers Explained</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/confusion-matrix-for-security-classifiers-explained/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/confusion-matrix-for-security-classifiers-explained/" />
    <updated>2025-11-18T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to read a confusion matrix for security classifiers, compare metrics like precision and recall, and interpret errors to improve intrusion and malware detection decisions.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence with Power BI: A Hands-On Guide</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-with-power-bi-a-hands-on-guide/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-with-power-bi-a-hands-on-guide/" />
    <updated>2025-11-18T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to add AI to Power BI step by step. Plan architecture, prepare data, build AutoML and DAX-based signals, then govern and monitor deployment in production reports.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Fraud Risk Modeling with AI: Features, Models, and MRM</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/fraud-risk-modeling-with-ai-features-models-and-mrm/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/fraud-risk-modeling-with-ai-features-models-and-mrm/" />
    <updated>2025-11-18T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to plan, build, and validate AI-driven fraud risk models in financial services with features, algorithms, MRM controls, and practical troubleshooting.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Assortment Optimization with AI for Retailers: Tactics</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/assortment-optimization-with-ai-for-retailers-tactics/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/assortment-optimization-with-ai-for-retailers-tactics/" />
    <updated>2025-11-18T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow a practical, step by step path to build AI driven assortment optimization for retail, from planning and data setup to deployment, validation, and ongoing tuning.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is Intelligent Street Lighting? A Clear, Quick Answer</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-intelligent-street-lighting-a-clear-quick-answer/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-intelligent-street-lighting-a-clear-quick-answer/" />
    <updated>2025-11-18T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what intelligent street lighting is, how it works from pole to cloud, when it fits, implementation steps, and practical alternatives that support safer, energy efficient streets.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI’s Role in Detection Pipelines: Nuance and Limits</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ais-role-in-detection-pipelines-nuance-and-limits/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ais-role-in-detection-pipelines-nuance-and-limits/" />
    <updated>2025-11-17T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand where AI excels and where it falls short in detection pipelines. Learn definitions, decision lenses, and practical tradeoffs to design dependable security workflows.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Analytics AI: Building Smarter Pipelines and Models</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/analytics-ai-building-smarter-pipelines-and-models/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/analytics-ai-building-smarter-pipelines-and-models/" />
    <updated>2025-11-17T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how analytics AI upgrades data pipelines, feature stores, and models into reliable dashboards and decisions. See architecture choices, tools, patterns, and governance guardrails.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Detect Fraud with ML in Banking: A Field Guide</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/detect-fraud-with-ml-in-banking-a-field-guide/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/detect-fraud-with-ml-in-banking-a-field-guide/" />
    <updated>2025-11-17T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Step-by-step guide to detect fraud in banking with machine learning. Plan data, build features, train models, validate, and tune thresholds with governance and monitoring in mind.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Retail Solutions: Choose the Right Stack for Scale</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-retail-solutions-choose-the-right-stack-for-scale/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-retail-solutions-choose-the-right-stack-for-scale/" />
    <updated>2025-11-17T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare build, buy, and hybrid AI retail solutions across accuracy, cost, speed, and governance. Learn how to weigh data maturity, integration paths, and long‑term scale to pick the right stack.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Urban Lighting: Design Patterns for Safer Streets</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-urban-lighting-design-patterns-for-safer-streets/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-urban-lighting-design-patterns-for-safer-streets/" />
    <updated>2025-11-17T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand smart urban lighting design patterns that improve safety, reduce energy, and guide movement. Learn definitions, selection frameworks, examples, and limits to inform city and campus upgrades with confidence.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI System Architecture for Detection Workflows</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-system-architecture-for-detection-workflows/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-system-architecture-for-detection-workflows/" />
    <updated>2025-11-16T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to design AI system architecture for detection workflows. See components, data flows, model gating, and governance that improve speed, accuracy, and resilience.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI-Powered Business Intelligence: 20 Smart Features</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-powered-business-intelligence-20-smart-features/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-powered-business-intelligence-20-smart-features/" />
    <updated>2025-11-16T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore 20 AI-powered business intelligence features that elevate dashboards, decisions, and data workflows, with tradeoffs, guardrails, and examples to guide practical adoption in real organizations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Anomaly Detection in Finance with AI: Methods That Scale</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/anomaly-detection-in-finance-with-ai-methods-that-scale/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/anomaly-detection-in-finance-with-ai-methods-that-scale/" />
    <updated>2025-11-16T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn a step by step path to implement AI anomaly detection in finance with sound data prep, model choices, metrics, and controls that scale across teams.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Predictive Analytics for Retail: From Data to Action</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-predictive-analytics-for-retail-from-data-to-action/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-predictive-analytics-for-retail-from-data-to-action/" />
    <updated>2025-11-16T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to plan, build, and validate AI predictive analytics for retail. Follow clear steps to turn data into demand forecasts, smarter replenishment, and measurable in‑stock improvements.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Lamp: Components, Capabilities, and Uses</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lamp-components-capabilities-and-uses/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lamp-components-capabilities-and-uses/" />
    <updated>2025-11-16T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a smart street lamp works, from LED heads and sensors to controls and networking, plus capabilities, tradeoffs, and practical urban uses.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Programming with Python for Security Workflows</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-programming-with-python-for-security-workflows/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-programming-with-python-for-security-workflows/" />
    <updated>2025-11-15T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build a practical Python workflow for AI-driven security detection. Plan data, set up tools, train models, validate with ROC AUC and confusion matrices, and troubleshoot edge cases for reliable outcomes.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI-Driven Business Intelligence: What Changes and Why</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-driven-business-intelligence-what-changes-and-why/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-driven-business-intelligence-what-changes-and-why/" />
    <updated>2025-11-15T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI-driven business intelligence reshapes analytics with augmented workflows, smarter dashboards, and a robust architecture for governance, monitoring, and value measurement across decisions, forecasts, and operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AML Transaction Monitoring with AI: Speed and Precision</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/aml-transaction-monitoring-with-ai-speed-and-precision/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/aml-transaction-monitoring-with-ai-speed-and-precision/" />
    <updated>2025-11-15T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI elevates AML transaction monitoring with faster detection, fewer false positives, and stronger investigations while meeting regulatory expectations and model risk controls.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Retail and CPG: Shared Data, Shared Advantage</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-and-cpg-shared-data-shared-advantage/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-and-cpg-shared-data-shared-advantage/" />
    <updated>2025-11-15T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI ties retail and CPG partners through shared data, common metrics, and governance to improve forecasts, replenishment, and assortments while respecting privacy and control.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Public Lighting: Policy, Design, and Equity Considerations</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-public-lighting-policy-design-and-equity-considerations/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-public-lighting-policy-design-and-equity-considerations/" />
    <updated>2025-11-15T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how smart public lighting policy, human-centered design, and equity guardrails shape safer, energy-efficient streets while protecting privacy and access for every neighborhood.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Programming Languages for Cyber Detection: Compare</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-programming-languages-for-cyber-detection-compare/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-programming-languages-for-cyber-detection-compare/" />
    <updated>2025-11-14T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare Python, Go, and Rust for AI-driven cyber detection. Weigh speed, safety, libraries, deployment, and data workflows to match your team and threat model.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Power BI: Bring Predictions Into Every Report</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-power-bi-bring-predictions-into-every-report/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-power-bi-bring-predictions-into-every-report/" />
    <updated>2025-11-14T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn practical ways to add predictions to Power BI using built-in AI, custom models, and M or DAX patterns. See architecture, deployment, and design tips for trustworthy dashboards.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Loan Companies: Who’s Innovating and How They Win</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-loan-companies-whos-innovating-and-how-they-win/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-loan-companies-whos-innovating-and-how-they-win/" />
    <updated>2025-11-14T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore six ways AI loan companies innovate across underwriting, fraud, pricing, collections, and governance, with examples, tradeoffs, and controls that keep decisions fast, fair, and compliant.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI + ML in Retail: Data Pipelines, Models, and Outcomes</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-ml-in-retail-data-pipelines-models-and-outcomes/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-ml-in-retail-data-pipelines-models-and-outcomes/" />
    <updated>2025-11-14T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI and ML improve retail outcomes by building the right data pipelines, selecting fit-for-purpose models, and translating predictions into decisions.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart City Street Lights Sensors: Types and Placement</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-city-street-lights-sensors-types-and-placement/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-city-street-lights-sensors-types-and-placement/" />
    <updated>2025-11-14T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn sensor types used in smart city street lights, how they work, optimal placement, and tradeoffs that balance safety, privacy, and maintenance.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Programming Language Choices for Security Teams</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-programming-language-choices-for-security-teams/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-programming-language-choices-for-security-teams/" />
    <updated>2025-11-13T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare Python, Go, and Rust for security AI work. Learn criteria, tradeoffs, and scenarios to pick the right language for detection pipelines and tooling.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Analytics: From Descriptive to Predictive</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-analytics-from-descriptive-to-predictive/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-analytics-from-descriptive-to-predictive/" />
    <updated>2025-11-13T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI elevates analytics from descriptive reports to predictive insight. Explore data architecture, practical tools, and dashboard patterns with examples, tradeoffs, and governance guidance for reliable decision support.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Finance and Investing: Signals, Risk, and Returns</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-finance-and-investing-signals-risk-and-returns/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-finance-and-investing-signals-risk-and-returns/" />
    <updated>2025-11-13T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand how AI interprets financial signals, manages risk, and targets returns with clear frameworks, examples, and limitations to guide finance and investing decisions responsibly.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Machine Learning in Retail: Forecasts, Stock, and Assortment</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-retail-forecasts-stock-and-assortment/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-retail-forecasts-stock-and-assortment/" />
    <updated>2025-11-13T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how machine learning strengthens retail forecasts, inventory planning, replenishment, planograms, and assortments, with practical guardrails, workflows, edge cases, and links to deeper guides for fast operational wins.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart City Street Lighting: Capabilities and Use Cases</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-city-street-lighting-capabilities-and-use-cases/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-city-street-lighting-capabilities-and-use-cases/" />
    <updated>2025-11-13T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what smart city street lighting can do, how capabilities map to real use cases, and the decisions that guide upgrades from pilots to citywide deployment.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Engine Design for Security Pipelines: Principles</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-engine-design-for-security-pipelines-principles/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-engine-design-for-security-pipelines-principles/" />
    <updated>2025-11-12T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn core principles for AI engine design in security pipelines, from modular architecture to evaluation and risk controls, with practical tradeoffs and examples.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Business Analytics: From Hunches to Confidence</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-analytics-from-hunches-to-confidence/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-analytics-from-hunches-to-confidence/" />
    <updated>2025-11-12T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI business analytics upgrades dashboards and reporting with predictive models, explainability, and guardrails. See architecture patterns, tool choices, and a small code example that feeds practical decisions.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Banking and Finance: Capabilities and Constraints</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-banking-and-finance-capabilities-and-constraints/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-banking-and-finance-capabilities-and-constraints/" />
    <updated>2025-11-12T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what AI can and cannot do in banking and finance, with clear definitions, decision frameworks, practical scenarios, and risk-aware tradeoffs for teams building reliable solutions.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Retail Voice AI: Design Conversational Commerce that Helps</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-voice-ai-design-conversational-commerce-that-helps/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-voice-ai-design-conversational-commerce-that-helps/" />
    <updated>2025-11-12T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how retail voice AI improves shopper journeys, from intent capture to guided dialogs, with design lenses, examples, and tradeoffs that balance accuracy, privacy, and conversion.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart City Lighting: Where It Fits and How It Scales</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-city-lighting-where-it-fits-and-how-it-scales/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-city-lighting-where-it-fits-and-how-it-scales/" />
    <updated>2025-11-12T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn where smart city lighting fits in urban programs, how it scales from pilots to districts, and the governance, networking, and data choices that shape outcomes.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Data Management for Security Models: Checklists</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-management-for-security-models-checklists/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-management-for-security-models-checklists/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical checklists for AI data management in security models, covering inventory, versioning, quality validation, privacy governance, and class balance with leakage-safe workflows.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI and ML in Business: 35 Practical, Proved Use Cases</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-ml-in-business-35-practical-proved-use-cases/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-ml-in-business-35-practical-proved-use-cases/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore 35 practical AI and ML use cases that deliver measurable business value across sales, marketing, finance, operations, and customer service with risk-aware guidance.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Fraud Detection vs Rule-Based: What Performs Better?</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-fraud-detection-vs-rule-based-what-performs-better/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-fraud-detection-vs-rule-based-what-performs-better/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare AI fraud detection with rule-based systems using accuracy, latency, cost, explainability, and governance. Learn tradeoffs, where each fits, and how to phase adoption with risk controls that satisfy auditors and operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Retail Conversational AI: Platforms and Key Tradeoffs</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-conversational-ai-platforms-and-key-tradeoffs/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-conversational-ai-platforms-and-key-tradeoffs/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare retail conversational AI platforms across suites, composable toolkits, and open source. Learn evaluation criteria, tradeoffs, and best-fit scenarios to guide confident platform selection.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Intelligent Street Lighting: How It Works From Pole to Cloud</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-how-it-works-from-pole-to-cloud/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-how-it-works-from-pole-to-cloud/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how intelligent street lighting works from pole to cloud with planning steps, device setup, network choices, validation checks, and fixes for common issues.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>End-to-End Intrusion Detection Pipeline with AI</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/end-to-end-intrusion-detection-pipeline-with-ai/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/end-to-end-intrusion-detection-pipeline-with-ai/" />
    <updated>2025-11-10T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design a practical intrusion detection pipeline with AI, from data intake and feature engineering to model evaluation using confusion matrices and ROC AUC, plus deployment patterns and safeguards.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI + BI: Architecting Insight That Scales and Learns</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-plus-bi-architecting-insight-that-scales-and-learns/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-plus-bi-architecting-insight-that-scales-and-learns/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T03:40:14Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Design AI with BI to move from static reports to evolving insight. Learn architecture, feature pipelines, model governance, and dashboard patterns that scale across teams.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Risk Management: From Fraud Flags to MRM Controls</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-risk-management-from-fraud-flags-to-mrm-controls/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-risk-management-from-fraud-flags-to-mrm-controls/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T03:40:14Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practitioner guide to AI in financial risk management covering fraud detection, AML, anomaly detection, monitoring workflows, and model risk management controls you can operationalize.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Retail AI Companies: The Innovators to Watch This Year</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-ai-companies-the-innovators-to-watch-this-year/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-ai-companies-the-innovators-to-watch-this-year/" />
    <updated>2025-11-10T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore seven types of retail AI innovators shaping search, checkout, personalization, pricing, and operations. Learn fit, examples, and tradeoffs to guide your roadmap this year.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Intelligent Street Lighting Advantages: The Top 10 to Track</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-advantages-the-top-10-to-track/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-advantages-the-top-10-to-track/" />
    <updated>2025-11-10T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore ten intelligent street lighting advantages with examples, tradeoffs, and selection tips. Learn where smart controls improve safety, cut energy, and support citywide operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is AI in Cybersecurity? A Clear, Practical View</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-in-cybersecurity-a-clear-practical-view/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-in-cybersecurity-a-clear-practical-view/" />
    <updated>2025-11-09T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI supports cybersecurity with detection, triage, and response. See tradeoffs, when to apply models, a small scoring example, and validation tips for SOC operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Which AI Software Is Best for Small Business Today?</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/which-ai-software-is-best-for-small-business-today/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/which-ai-software-is-best-for-small-business-today/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T03:40:14Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how small businesses can compare AI software by use case, cost, data risk, and speed to value. Learn a simple framework, practical picks, and a phased rollout that avoids waste.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is AI Financial Forecasting? Definitions and Examples</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-financial-forecasting-definitions-and-examples/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-financial-forecasting-definitions-and-examples/" />
    <updated>2025-11-11T03:40:14Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI financial forecasting works, where it delivers value, pitfalls to avoid, and a practical validation workflow with examples and guardrails.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Online Shopping AI: Personalization That Feels Natural</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/online-shopping-ai-personalization-that-feels-natural/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/online-shopping-ai-personalization-that-feels-natural/" />
    <updated>2025-11-09T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how online shopping AI delivers personalization that feels natural, balancing relevance with privacy, cold-start tactics, and measurement frameworks that avoid creepiness while improving conversions and lifetime value.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>How Smart Street Lighting Improves Safety: Evidence and Tactics</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-smart-street-lighting-improves-safety-evidence-and-tactics/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-smart-street-lighting-improves-safety-evidence-and-tactics/" />
    <updated>2025-11-09T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how smart street lighting improves safety through better visibility, data driven dimming, and faster maintenance, with practical tactics and validation methods cities can apply.]]></summary>
  </entry>
</feed>