<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>PulseGeek</title>
  <id>https://pulsegeek.com/atom.xml</id>
  <updated>2025-10-29T14:16:00Z</updated>
  <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://pulsegeek.com" />
  <author>
    <name>PulseGeek</name>
  </author>
  <subtitle>Tech news, gaming, and geek culture in one pulse</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Data Security Tactics: Protecting Models and Signals</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-security-tactics-protecting-models-and-signals/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-security-tactics-protecting-models-and-signals/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical AI data security tactics to protect training signals, model artifacts, and SOC analytics. Learn controls for privacy, integrity, governance, and resilient operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Business Services: What SMBs Can Outsource First</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-services-what-smbs-can-outsource-first/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-services-what-smbs-can-outsource-first/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover nine AI business services SMBs can outsource first. See concrete examples, selection tips, and tradeoffs to cut cost while protecting quality.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in FP&amp;A: 12 High-Impact Opportunities to Pursue</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-fpa-12-high-impact-opportunities-to-pursue/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-fpa-12-high-impact-opportunities-to-pursue/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore twelve practical AI opportunities for FP&A that raise forecast accuracy, speed decisions, and strengthen controls. Learn where to start, what to measure, and tradeoffs to consider.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Convenience Store: Speed, Selection, and Trust</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-convenience-store-speed-selection-and-trust/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-convenience-store-speed-selection-and-trust/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI convenience stores balance rapid checkout, curated selection, and shopper trust using data, sensors, and design choices that reduce friction and increase confidence.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Street Light Automation System: From Pilot to Rollout</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-light-automation-system-from-pilot-to-rollout/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-light-automation-system-from-pilot-to-rollout/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plan, configure, and scale a street light automation system from a small pilot to citywide rollout with steps, checks, and fixes.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Checkpoints for Security Teams: Readiness and Risk</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-checkpoints-for-security-teams-readiness-and-risk/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-checkpoints-for-security-teams-readiness-and-risk/" />
    <updated>2025-10-28T14:17:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn practical AI checkpoints for security teams to gauge readiness, control risk, and align governance with SOC outcomes. Identify coverage gaps, data quality issues, and decision thresholds before scaling automation.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Applications for Small Business: 28 Quick Wins</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-applications-for-small-business-28-quick-wins/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-applications-for-small-business-28-quick-wins/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover 28 practical AI applications for small business, from lead routing and pricing to service quality and cash flow. Learn tradeoffs, setup tips, and fast validation steps.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Financial Services: Capabilities Across the Value Chain</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-financial-services-capabilities-across-the-value-chain/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-financial-services-capabilities-across-the-value-chain/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how AI reshapes financial services from onboarding to risk, forecasting, and reporting. Learn decision frameworks, examples, and tradeoffs to deploy capabilities with control and measurable value.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Shopping: Conversational Journeys and Smart Checkout</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-shopping-conversational-journeys-and-smart-checkout/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-shopping-conversational-journeys-and-smart-checkout/" />
    <updated>2025-10-28T14:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how AI for shopping powers conversational journeys and smart checkout. Learn core patterns, workflows, risks, and choices to boost conversion and satisfaction.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>ZK-STARKs vs SNARKs: Security, Speed, and Setups</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-starks-vs-snarks-security-speed-and-setups/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-starks-vs-snarks-security-speed-and-setups/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare ZK-STARKs and SNARKs across security assumptions, proving speed, verification costs, proof sizes, and trusted setups to choose the best fit for privacy and scaling.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Lighting Solution: What to Include and Why</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-solution-what-to-include-and-why/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-solution-what-to-include-and-why/" />
    <updated>2025-10-28T14:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build a smart street lighting solution that balances safety and savings. Learn what to include from controls and sensors to dimming profiles, metering, and maintenance.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Basics for Security: Foundation and Boundaries</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-basics-for-security-foundation-and-boundaries/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-basics-for-security-foundation-and-boundaries/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T14:17:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the core AI building blocks for security, when to apply them, and where their boundaries lie. Get decision lenses, practical examples, and limits that shape effective SOC analytics.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>SMB AI Playbook: Affordable Wins That Drive Growth</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smb-ai-playbook-affordable-wins-that-drive-growth/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smb-ai-playbook-affordable-wins-that-drive-growth/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practical guide to AI for small business. Prioritize quick wins, choose budget tools, prepare data, avoid pitfalls, and roll out a roadmap that compounds growth across marketing, sales, and operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Corporate Finance: Capital Decisions with Confidence</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-corporate-finance-capital-decisions-with-confidence/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-corporate-finance-capital-decisions-with-confidence/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI helps corporate finance teams make capital allocation decisions with clarity, quantify risk, and align investments to strategy using explainable methods, guardrails, and practical scoring frameworks.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is AI in Retail? Definitions, Uses, and Benefits</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-in-retail-definitions-uses-and-benefits/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-in-retail-definitions-uses-and-benefits/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T14:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what AI in retail means, core uses across merchandising and operations, and measurable benefits with practical guidance for implementation, governance, and validation.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>ZK-SNARKs Explained: Proving More with Less Data</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-snarks-explained-proving-more-with-less-data/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-snarks-explained-proving-more-with-less-data/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how ZK-SNARKs let you prove statements without revealing inputs, compress many computations into tiny proofs, and verify quickly. See privacy, scalability, and setup tradeoffs explained with clear steps and a toy example.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Light Technology: From Nodes to Power Meters</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-technology-from-nodes-to-power-meters/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-technology-from-nodes-to-power-meters/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T14:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how smart street light technology fits together, from controllers and sensors to metering and backhaul, with tradeoffs, examples, and practical decision lenses.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Cybersecurity: From SOC Signals to Smart Defense</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-cybersecurity-from-soc-signals-to-smart-defense/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-cybersecurity-from-soc-signals-to-smart-defense/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI strengthens cybersecurity across SOC workflows, from signal design and modeling choices to deployment guardrails, evaluation, and real-world response patterns for resilient defense.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Where Artificial Intelligence Is Used in Business Today</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/where-artificial-intelligence-is-used-in-business-today/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/where-artificial-intelligence-is-used-in-business-today/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore where artificial intelligence is used in business today, from marketing and sales to operations, finance, and risk. See integration patterns, guardrails, and governance for measurable impact.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Financial Reporting: 15 Ways to Speed Close with Trust</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-reporting-15-ways-to-speed-close-with-trust/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-reporting-15-ways-to-speed-close-with-trust/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover 15 practical AI techniques for financial reporting that accelerate close, improve accuracy, tighten controls, and enhance audit readiness while preserving transparency.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Use of AI in Retail: Core Functions and Outcomes</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-use-of-ai-in-retail-core-functions-and-outcomes/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-use-of-ai-in-retail-core-functions-and-outcomes/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand how AI reshapes retail across demand planning, pricing, content, and service. Learn core functions, decision lenses, and tangible outcomes with practical tradeoffs operators and merchants can use to prioritize investments.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>ZK Rollups: 8 Designs Compressing Blockchain Traffic</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-rollups-8-designs-compressing-blockchain-traffic/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-rollups-8-designs-compressing-blockchain-traffic/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore eight zk rollup designs that compress on-chain traffic, cut gas, and preserve security. Learn how proofs, data availability, and zkEVM choices shape performance and developer experience.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Light Sensors: Types, Accuracy, and Placement</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-sensors-types-accuracy-and-placement/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-sensors-types-accuracy-and-placement/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn which smart street light sensors to use, how accurate they are, and where to mount them for reliable detection, energy savings, and safe visibility.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is NLP for Email Security? A Practical Primer</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-nlp-for-email-security-a-practical-primer/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-nlp-for-email-security-a-practical-primer/" />
    <updated>2025-10-25T14:17:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how NLP improves email security with content and URL analysis, evaluation methods, and practical implementation patterns. Compare fit, limits, and validation tips.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Using AI for Business: Start Small, Measure, Expand</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/using-ai-for-business-start-small-measure-expand/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/using-ai-for-business-start-small-measure-expand/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use AI for business with a stepwise playbook. Pick one use case, set a baseline, pilot safely, measure outcomes, and scale what works.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Financial Forecasting &amp; FP&amp;A: Methods, Controls, ROI</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-forecasting-and-fpa-methods-controls-roi/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-forecasting-and-fpa-methods-controls-roi/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practitioner guide to AI financial forecasting for FP&A. Learn methods, controls, workflows, pitfalls, and how to size ROI with data-driven decisions and governance.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Retailers Using AI: Who’s Leading and What They Do</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retailers-using-ai-whos-leading-and-what-they-do/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retailers-using-ai-whos-leading-and-what-they-do/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how leading retailers use AI across pricing, forecasting, personalization, and store operations, with concrete examples, patterns to copy, and practical tradeoffs.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>PLONK ZK Proof: From Arithmetization to Verification</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plonk-zk-proof-from-arithmetization-to-verification/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plonk-zk-proof-from-arithmetization-to-verification/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a PLONK zk proof is built end to end. Map logic to circuits, encode constraints as polynomials, and walk through proving and verification steps with practical tips.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Light Control: Methods, Modes, and Triggers</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-methods-modes-and-triggers/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-methods-modes-and-triggers/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn smart street light control methods, operating modes, and sensor triggers with decision lenses, scenarios, and tradeoffs that balance safety, savings, and maintainability.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Text Classification Techniques for Phishing Emails</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/text-classification-techniques-for-phishing-emails/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/text-classification-techniques-for-phishing-emails/" />
    <updated>2025-10-25T19:47:43Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore eleven proven text classification techniques for phishing emails, with examples, tradeoffs, and practical guidance for reliable detection.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Integrating AI into Business Systems Without Disruption</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/integrating-ai-into-business-systems-without-disruption/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/integrating-ai-into-business-systems-without-disruption/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow a stepwise path for integrating AI into business systems without downtime. Scope seams, define data contracts, build safe APIs, and scale with canaries and measurable ROI.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is Intelligent Document Processing for Finance?</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-intelligent-document-processing-for-finance/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-intelligent-document-processing-for-finance/" />
    <updated>2025-10-24T19:46:24Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how intelligent document processing streamlines finance workflows by extracting, validating, and routing invoices, receipts, and statements with controls that satisfy audit, risk, and data quality needs.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Retail AI Software Comparison: Platforms and Fit</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-ai-software-comparison-platforms-and-fit/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-ai-software-comparison-platforms-and-fit/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare retail AI software types with clear criteria, tradeoffs, and scenarios. Learn where platforms, point solutions, or cloud services best fit and why.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Mina Protocol: A Tiny Blockchain with Big ZK Ideas</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-protocol-a-tiny-blockchain-with-big-zk-ideas/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-protocol-a-tiny-blockchain-with-big-zk-ideas/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how Mina Protocol keeps the chain light with recursive proofs, enabling privacy and compression through zero-knowledge while preserving decentralization and practical verification on everyday devices.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart LED Street Lighting: 9 Options Cities Evaluate</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-led-street-lighting-9-options-cities-evaluate/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-led-street-lighting-9-options-cities-evaluate/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore nine smart LED street lighting options cities compare, with examples, tradeoffs, and configuration tips to balance safety, savings, and maintainability.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Spear Phishing Detection: AI Features That Matter</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/spear-phishing-detection-ai-features-that-matter/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/spear-phishing-detection-ai-features-that-matter/" />
    <updated>2025-10-25T19:47:43Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover spear phishing detection features that matter for AI models, with concrete examples, tradeoffs, and practical signals spanning content, sender, headers, URLs, and behavior.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Implementing AI in Business: A Step-by-Step Playbook</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/implementing-ai-in-business-a-step-by-step-playbook/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/implementing-ai-in-business-a-step-by-step-playbook/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow a practical playbook for implementing AI in business. Identify high-value use cases, assess data and risk, integrate solutions, run pilots, measure impact, and scale responsibly.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Vendor Invoice Matching with ML: Reduce Exceptions Fast</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vendor-invoice-matching-with-ml-reduce-exceptions-fast/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vendor-invoice-matching-with-ml-reduce-exceptions-fast/" />
    <updated>2025-10-24T19:46:24Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to implement machine learning for vendor invoice matching in accounting. Plan data, configure models, validate results, and reduce exceptions with controls and auditability.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Plan AI Projects in Retail Operations: Roadmaps That Work</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plan-ai-projects-in-retail-operations-roadmaps-that-work/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plan-ai-projects-in-retail-operations-roadmaps-that-work/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to plan AI projects in retail operations with a proven roadmap. Scope problems, ready data, execute pilots, validate results, and scale responsibly.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Future of AI in Learning: Adaptive, Fair, and Trusted</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-future-of-ai-in-learning-adaptive-fair-and-trusted/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-future-of-ai-in-learning-adaptive-fair-and-trusted/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the future of AI in learning with adaptive paths, fair assessment, and integrity safeguards, plus clear ties to machine learning concepts and practical rollout steps.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Mina Crypto: 9 Reasons ZK Natives Are Watching</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-crypto-9-reasons-zk-natives-are-watching/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-crypto-9-reasons-zk-natives-are-watching/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore why ZK builders track Mina crypto. Learn how a tiny chain, recursive proofs, and private zkApps enable verifiable compute, light clients, and practical privacy tradeoffs.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sensor Street Lamp: Choosing Motion, Ambient, and Radar</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/sensor-street-lamp-choosing-motion-ambient-and-radar/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/sensor-street-lamp-choosing-motion-ambient-and-radar/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to choose motion, ambient light, and radar sensors for street lamps, including placement rules, tuning ranges, and control logic tradeoffs for safety and savings.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Open Artificial Intelligence in Email Security</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/open-artificial-intelligence-in-email-security/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/open-artificial-intelligence-in-email-security/" />
    <updated>2025-10-25T19:47:43Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how open artificial intelligence advances email security using transparent models, evaluable features, and interoperable tooling, with tradeoffs around data privacy, robustness, and governance in production.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>How to Implement AI in Business: A Practical Guide</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-implement-ai-in-business-a-practical-guide/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-implement-ai-in-business-a-practical-guide/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to implement AI in business with a practical roadmap that selects the right use cases, integrates responsibly, measures outcomes, and scales value.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Use AI for Account Reconciliation: A Practical Blueprint</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/use-ai-for-account-reconciliation-a-practical-blueprint/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/use-ai-for-account-reconciliation-a-practical-blueprint/" />
    <updated>2025-10-24T19:46:24Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn a step-by-step method to use AI for account reconciliation, from planning and data prep to matching logic, validation, and controls, with examples and troubleshooting tips for finance teams.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>How Is AI Used in Retail Merchandising? A Practical Guide</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-is-ai-used-in-retail-merchandising-a-practical-guide/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-is-ai-used-in-retail-merchandising-a-practical-guide/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to apply AI in retail merchandising with clear steps, setup tips, validation methods, and fixes. Plan your use cases, prepare data, run experiments, and measure results responsibly.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Personalized Learning with AI: Design Blueprints That Work</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/personalized-learning-with-ai-design-blueprints-that-work/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/personalized-learning-with-ai-design-blueprints-that-work/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn a practical blueprint for personalized learning with AI. Define outcomes and signals, build adaptive paths, design fair assessments, and measure impact while safeguarding privacy and academic integrity.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Zero-Knowledge Proofs: Privacy and Proof Without Sharing</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zero-knowledge-proofs-privacy-and-proof-without-sharing/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zero-knowledge-proofs-privacy-and-proof-without-sharing/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how zero knowledge proofs deliver privacy and compression by proving facts without revealing data, and see where SNARKs, STARKs, and rollups fit. Practical guidance, choices, and pitfalls for builders.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Intelligent Wireless Street Lighting Systems: Key Choices</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-wireless-street-lighting-systems-key-choices/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-wireless-street-lighting-systems-key-choices/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how intelligent wireless street lighting systems work, key design tradeoffs, sensor choices, and control strategies to balance savings, safety, and maintainability.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>NLP Essentials for Security: Language Meets Signals</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/nlp-essentials-for-security-language-meets-signals/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/nlp-essentials-for-security-language-meets-signals/" />
    <updated>2025-10-25T19:47:43Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how natural language processing connects text understanding with email and network signals to improve phishing detection, triage, and response in practical security workflows.]]></summary>
  </entry>
</feed>