<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>PulseGeek</title>
  <id>https://pulsegeek.com/atom.xml</id>
  <updated>2025-11-02T16:16:00Z</updated>
  <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/atom.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://pulsegeek.com" />
  <author>
    <name>PulseGeek</name>
  </author>
  <subtitle>Tech news, gaming, and geek culture in one pulse</subtitle>
  <entry>
    <title>Artificial Intelligence in Security: Core Concepts</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-security-core-concepts/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-security-core-concepts/" />
    <updated>2025-11-02T16:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the core concepts of artificial intelligence in security, including detection signals, model choices, thresholds, evaluation, and human oversight to build reliable SOC analytics and resilient defenses.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Small Business Marketing: Tactics That Convert</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-small-business-marketing-tactics-that-convert/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-small-business-marketing-tactics-that-convert/" />
    <updated>2025-11-02T16:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A stepwise playbook for small business marketing with AI. Prioritize use cases, prepare data, run lean experiments, and measure lift to scale what converts.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Generative AI in Finance: Use Cases, Limits, and Guardrails</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-finance-use-cases-limits-and-guardrails/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-finance-use-cases-limits-and-guardrails/" />
    <updated>2025-11-02T16:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how generative AI fits finance workflows, with practical use cases, risk limits, and governance guardrails that preserve accuracy, compliance, and stakeholder trust.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Amazon Go AI: Tech Behind Just Walk Out Experiences</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-go-ai-tech-behind-just-walk-out-experiences/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-go-ai-tech-behind-just-walk-out-experiences/" />
    <updated>2025-11-02T16:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore the technology powering Just Walk Out at Amazon Go, including sensor fusion, identity, and privacy safeguards, with decision frameworks and practical tradeoffs for retailers evaluating similar systems.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Lighting: Citywide Benefits, Safety, and Design</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-citywide-benefits-safety-and-design/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-citywide-benefits-safety-and-design/" />
    <updated>2025-11-02T16:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Get a practitioner-grade overview of smart street lighting, covering citywide benefits, safety impacts, design choices, and integration with broader smart city programs.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI-Driven SOC Analytics Techniques You Can Apply Now</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-driven-soc-analytics-techniques-you-can-apply-now/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-driven-soc-analytics-techniques-you-can-apply-now/" />
    <updated>2025-11-01T14:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical SOC analytics techniques using AI to enrich telemetry, build behavior baselines, correlate signals, and close the loop with feedback. Learn tradeoffs, examples, and steps to apply safely.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Entrepreneurs: Leverage, Focus, and Momentum</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-entrepreneurs-leverage-focus-and-momentum/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-entrepreneurs-leverage-focus-and-momentum/" />
    <updated>2025-11-01T14:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn practical ways entrepreneurs can use AI to create leverage, choose high impact workflows, pick sane tools, and build compounding momentum without overspending.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Finance AI Explained: Data, Models, and Value Realization</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/finance-ai-explained-data-models-and-value-realization/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/finance-ai-explained-data-models-and-value-realization/" />
    <updated>2025-11-01T14:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how finance AI turns raw data into useful models and measurable value. See definitions, decision frameworks, examples, risks, and steps to link analytics with controls and business outcomes.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Amazon AI Store: Lessons from Frictionless Shopping</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-store-lessons-from-frictionless-shopping/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-store-lessons-from-frictionless-shopping/" />
    <updated>2025-11-01T14:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn practical lessons from frictionless shopping in Amazon-style AI stores. Understand definitions, decision lenses, and tradeoffs to evaluate readiness, reduce friction, and prioritize improvements without overspending on unproven technology.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Wireless Street Light Control Systems: Topologies Compared</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/wireless-street-light-control-systems-topologies-compared/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/wireless-street-light-control-systems-topologies-compared/" />
    <updated>2025-11-01T14:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how wireless street light control system topologies differ, when to choose each, and the tradeoffs in latency, resilience, cost, and operations for city‑scale lighting.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Network Security Tools and Patterns to Know</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-network-security-tools-and-patterns-to-know/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-network-security-tools-and-patterns-to-know/" />
    <updated>2025-10-31T14:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore seven AI network security tools and patterns with examples, tradeoffs, and deployment tips for SOC analytics, anomaly detection, and resilient operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Business Growth: A Roadmap to Compounding ROI</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-growth-a-roadmap-to-compounding-roi/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-growth-a-roadmap-to-compounding-roi/" />
    <updated>2025-10-31T14:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use AI for business growth with a practical roadmap. Prioritize use cases, prep data, run measurable pilots, and scale wins for compounding ROI.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Explainable AI in Finance: Transparency Without Tradeoffs</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/explainable-ai-in-finance-transparency-without-tradeoffs/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/explainable-ai-in-finance-transparency-without-tradeoffs/" />
    <updated>2025-10-31T14:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how explainable AI brings clarity to finance models, balances risk and accuracy, and fits controls. Explore methods like SHAP, monotonicity, and surrogate models with practical decision criteria.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Amazon AI Grocery Store: Inventory, Vision, Checkout</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-grocery-store-inventory-vision-checkout/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-grocery-store-inventory-vision-checkout/" />
    <updated>2025-10-31T14:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI powers grocery inventory accuracy, computer vision for shelf insight, and low-friction checkout. See frameworks, scenarios, tradeoffs, and pragmatic guardrails that retailers can apply without copying any one vendor’s blueprint.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is a Street Light Dimming Profile? A Simple Explainer</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-street-light-dimming-profile-a-simple-explainer/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-street-light-dimming-profile-a-simple-explainer/" />
    <updated>2025-10-31T14:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what a street light dimming profile is, how it balances safety and savings, when to use it, and how to configure and verify schedules with sensors, rules, and real‑world constraints.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Cyber Security: Threat Models and Tuning</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-cyber-security-threat-models-and-tuning/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-cyber-security-threat-models-and-tuning/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T14:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to define practical threat models for AI in cyber security and tune detection systems with measurable criteria, guardrails, and risk-based decisions.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Business Development: Open More Right Doors</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-development-open-more-right-doors/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-development-open-more-right-doors/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T14:15:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover practical ways to use AI for business development. Learn ICP definition, data readiness, workflow design, scoring models, and outreach tactics that focus efforts and improve conversion with measurable results.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Build AI Forecasting Models for FP&amp;A: A Technical Guide</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-ai-forecasting-models-for-fpa-a-technical-guide/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-ai-forecasting-models-for-fpa-a-technical-guide/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T14:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow a practical, step by step path to design, train, and validate AI forecasting models for FP&A with controls, metrics, and troubleshooting tips that protect accuracy and trust.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Shopping: Guided Discovery and Confidence Cues</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-shopping-guided-discovery-and-confidence-cues/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-shopping-guided-discovery-and-confidence-cues/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T14:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI guides shopping discovery and builds confidence through intent signals, conversational helpers, and transparent cues that reduce friction and boost conversion.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Street Lighting Control System: Architecture and Options</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-lighting-control-system-architecture-and-options/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-lighting-control-system-architecture-and-options/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T14:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a street lighting control system is architected, key options from nodes to networks, and decision factors that balance savings, safety, and maintainability.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Data Security Tactics: Protecting Models and Signals</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-security-tactics-protecting-models-and-signals/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-security-tactics-protecting-models-and-signals/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:16:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Practical AI data security tactics to protect training signals, model artifacts, and SOC analytics. Learn controls for privacy, integrity, governance, and resilient operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Business Services: What SMBs Can Outsource First</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-services-what-smbs-can-outsource-first/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-services-what-smbs-can-outsource-first/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:55Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover nine AI business services SMBs can outsource first. See concrete examples, selection tips, and tradeoffs to cut cost while protecting quality.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in FP&amp;A: 12 High-Impact Opportunities to Pursue</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-fpa-12-high-impact-opportunities-to-pursue/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-fpa-12-high-impact-opportunities-to-pursue/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore twelve practical AI opportunities for FP&A that raise forecast accuracy, speed decisions, and strengthen controls. Learn where to start, what to measure, and tradeoffs to consider.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Convenience Store: Speed, Selection, and Trust</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-convenience-store-speed-selection-and-trust/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-convenience-store-speed-selection-and-trust/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:13:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI convenience stores balance rapid checkout, curated selection, and shopper trust using data, sensors, and design choices that reduce friction and increase confidence.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Street Light Automation System: From Pilot to Rollout</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-light-automation-system-from-pilot-to-rollout/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-light-automation-system-from-pilot-to-rollout/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T14:12:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Plan, configure, and scale a street light automation system from a small pilot to citywide rollout with steps, checks, and fixes.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Checkpoints for Security Teams: Readiness and Risk</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-checkpoints-for-security-teams-readiness-and-risk/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-checkpoints-for-security-teams-readiness-and-risk/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:55Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn practical AI checkpoints for security teams to gauge readiness, control risk, and align governance with SOC outcomes. Identify coverage gaps, data quality issues, and decision thresholds before scaling automation.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Applications for Small Business: 28 Quick Wins</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-applications-for-small-business-28-quick-wins/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-applications-for-small-business-28-quick-wins/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:55Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover 28 practical AI applications for small business, from lead routing and pricing to service quality and cash flow. Learn tradeoffs, setup tips, and fast validation steps.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Financial Services: Capabilities Across the Value Chain</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-financial-services-capabilities-across-the-value-chain/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-financial-services-capabilities-across-the-value-chain/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how AI reshapes financial services from onboarding to risk, forecasting, and reporting. Learn decision frameworks, examples, and tradeoffs to deploy capabilities with control and measurable value.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI for Shopping: Conversational Journeys and Smart Checkout</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-shopping-conversational-journeys-and-smart-checkout/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-shopping-conversational-journeys-and-smart-checkout/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore how AI for shopping powers conversational journeys and smart checkout. Learn core patterns, workflows, risks, and choices to boost conversion and satisfaction.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>ZK-STARKs vs SNARKs: Security, Speed, and Setups</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-starks-vs-snarks-security-speed-and-setups/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-starks-vs-snarks-security-speed-and-setups/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compare ZK-STARKs and SNARKs across security assumptions, proving speed, verification costs, proof sizes, and trusted setups to choose the best fit for privacy and scaling.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Lighting Solution: What to Include and Why</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-solution-what-to-include-and-why/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-solution-what-to-include-and-why/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Build a smart street lighting solution that balances safety and savings. Learn what to include from controls and sensors to dimming profiles, metering, and maintenance.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Basics for Security: Foundation and Boundaries</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-basics-for-security-foundation-and-boundaries/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-basics-for-security-foundation-and-boundaries/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:55Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn the core AI building blocks for security, when to apply them, and where their boundaries lie. Get decision lenses, practical examples, and limits that shape effective SOC analytics.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>SMB AI Playbook: Affordable Wins That Drive Growth</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smb-ai-playbook-affordable-wins-that-drive-growth/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smb-ai-playbook-affordable-wins-that-drive-growth/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practical guide to AI for small business. Prioritize quick wins, choose budget tools, prepare data, avoid pitfalls, and roll out a roadmap that compounds growth across marketing, sales, and operations.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI in Corporate Finance: Capital Decisions with Confidence</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-corporate-finance-capital-decisions-with-confidence/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-corporate-finance-capital-decisions-with-confidence/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI helps corporate finance teams make capital allocation decisions with clarity, quantify risk, and align investments to strategy using explainable methods, guardrails, and practical scoring frameworks.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is AI in Retail? Definitions, Uses, and Benefits</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-in-retail-definitions-uses-and-benefits/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-ai-in-retail-definitions-uses-and-benefits/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T14:14:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn what AI in retail means, core uses across merchandising and operations, and measurable benefits with practical guidance for implementation, governance, and validation.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>ZK-SNARKs Explained: Proving More with Less Data</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-snarks-explained-proving-more-with-less-data/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-snarks-explained-proving-more-with-less-data/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how ZK-SNARKs let you prove statements without revealing inputs, compress many computations into tiny proofs, and verify quickly. See privacy, scalability, and setup tradeoffs explained with clear steps and a toy example.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Light Technology: From Nodes to Power Meters</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-technology-from-nodes-to-power-meters/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-technology-from-nodes-to-power-meters/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how smart street light technology fits together, from controllers and sensors to metering and backhaul, with tradeoffs, examples, and practical decision lenses.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Cybersecurity: From SOC Signals to Smart Defense</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-cybersecurity-from-soc-signals-to-smart-defense/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-cybersecurity-from-soc-signals-to-smart-defense/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how AI strengthens cybersecurity across SOC workflows, from signal design and modeling choices to deployment guardrails, evaluation, and real-world response patterns for resilient defense.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Where Artificial Intelligence Is Used in Business Today</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/where-artificial-intelligence-is-used-in-business-today/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/where-artificial-intelligence-is-used-in-business-today/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore where artificial intelligence is used in business today, from marketing and sales to operations, finance, and risk. See integration patterns, guardrails, and governance for measurable impact.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Financial Reporting: 15 Ways to Speed Close with Trust</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-reporting-15-ways-to-speed-close-with-trust/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-reporting-15-ways-to-speed-close-with-trust/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Discover 15 practical AI techniques for financial reporting that accelerate close, improve accuracy, tighten controls, and enhance audit readiness while preserving transparency.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>The Use of AI in Retail: Core Functions and Outcomes</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-use-of-ai-in-retail-core-functions-and-outcomes/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-use-of-ai-in-retail-core-functions-and-outcomes/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Understand how AI reshapes retail across demand planning, pricing, content, and service. Learn core functions, decision lenses, and tangible outcomes with practical tradeoffs operators and merchants can use to prioritize investments.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>ZK Rollups: 8 Designs Compressing Blockchain Traffic</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-rollups-8-designs-compressing-blockchain-traffic/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zk-rollups-8-designs-compressing-blockchain-traffic/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore eight zk rollup designs that compress on-chain traffic, cut gas, and preserve security. Learn how proofs, data availability, and zkEVM choices shape performance and developer experience.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Light Sensors: Types, Accuracy, and Placement</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-sensors-types-accuracy-and-placement/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-sensors-types-accuracy-and-placement/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn which smart street light sensors to use, how accurate they are, and where to mount them for reliable detection, energy savings, and safe visibility.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>What Is NLP for Email Security? A Practical Primer</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-nlp-for-email-security-a-practical-primer/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-nlp-for-email-security-a-practical-primer/" />
    <updated>2025-10-25T14:17:00Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how NLP improves email security with content and URL analysis, evaluation methods, and practical implementation patterns. Compare fit, limits, and validation tips.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Using AI for Business: Start Small, Measure, Expand</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/using-ai-for-business-start-small-measure-expand/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/using-ai-for-business-start-small-measure-expand/" />
    <updated>2025-10-27T03:27:21Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how to use AI for business with a stepwise playbook. Pick one use case, set a baseline, pilot safely, measure outcomes, and scale what works.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>AI Financial Forecasting &amp; FP&amp;A: Methods, Controls, ROI</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-forecasting-and-fpa-methods-controls-roi/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-forecasting-and-fpa-methods-controls-roi/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A practitioner guide to AI financial forecasting for FP&A. Learn methods, controls, workflows, pitfalls, and how to size ROI with data-driven decisions and governance.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Retailers Using AI: Who’s Leading and What They Do</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retailers-using-ai-whos-leading-and-what-they-do/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retailers-using-ai-whos-leading-and-what-they-do/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[See how leading retailers use AI across pricing, forecasting, personalization, and store operations, with concrete examples, patterns to copy, and practical tradeoffs.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>PLONK ZK Proof: From Arithmetization to Verification</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plonk-zk-proof-from-arithmetization-to-verification/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plonk-zk-proof-from-arithmetization-to-verification/" />
    <updated>2025-10-29T03:51:20Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn how a PLONK zk proof is built end to end. Map logic to circuits, encode constraints as polynomials, and walk through proving and verification steps with practical tips.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Smart Street Light Control: Methods, Modes, and Triggers</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-methods-modes-and-triggers/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-methods-modes-and-triggers/" />
    <updated>2025-10-30T04:19:56Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn smart street light control methods, operating modes, and sensor triggers with decision lenses, scenarios, and tradeoffs that balance safety, savings, and maintainability.]]></summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Text Classification Techniques for Phishing Emails</title>
    <id>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/text-classification-techniques-for-phishing-emails/</id>
    <link href="https://pulsegeek.com/articles/text-classification-techniques-for-phishing-emails/" />
    <updated>2025-10-25T19:47:43Z</updated>
    <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Explore eleven proven text classification techniques for phishing emails, with examples, tradeoffs, and practical guidance for reliable detection.]]></summary>
  </entry>
</feed>