<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PulseGeek</title>
    <link>https://pulsegeek.com</link>
    <description>Tech news, gaming, and geek culture in one pulse</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <generator>PulseGeek Rss Feed Generator</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pulsegeek.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Open Artificial Intelligence in Email Security</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/open-artificial-intelligence-in-email-security/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/open-artificial-intelligence-in-email-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how open artificial intelligence advances email security using transparent models, evaluable features, and interoperable tooling, with tradeoffs around data privacy, robustness, and governance in production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Implement AI in Business: A Practical Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-implement-ai-in-business-a-practical-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-implement-ai-in-business-a-practical-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to implement AI in business with a practical roadmap that selects the right use cases, integrates responsibly, measures outcomes, and scales value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use AI for Account Reconciliation: A Practical Blueprint</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/use-ai-for-account-reconciliation-a-practical-blueprint/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/use-ai-for-account-reconciliation-a-practical-blueprint/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn a step-by-step method to use AI for account reconciliation, from planning and data prep to matching logic, validation, and controls, with examples and troubleshooting tips for finance teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Is AI Used in Retail Merchandising? A Practical Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-is-ai-used-in-retail-merchandising-a-practical-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-is-ai-used-in-retail-merchandising-a-practical-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to apply AI in retail merchandising with clear steps, setup tips, validation methods, and fixes. Plan your use cases, prepare data, run experiments, and measure results responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Learning with AI: Design Blueprints That Work</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/personalized-learning-with-ai-design-blueprints-that-work/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/personalized-learning-with-ai-design-blueprints-that-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn a practical blueprint for personalized learning with AI. Define outcomes and signals, build adaptive paths, design fair assessments, and measure impact while safeguarding privacy and academic integrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Knowledge Proofs: Privacy and Proof Without Sharing</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zero-knowledge-proofs-privacy-and-proof-without-sharing/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zero-knowledge-proofs-privacy-and-proof-without-sharing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how zero knowledge proofs deliver privacy and compression by proving facts without revealing data, and see where SNARKs, STARKs, and rollups fit. Practical guidance, choices, and pitfalls for builders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Wireless Street Lighting Systems: Key Choices</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-wireless-street-lighting-systems-key-choices/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-wireless-street-lighting-systems-key-choices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how intelligent wireless street lighting systems work, key design tradeoffs, sensor choices, and control strategies to balance savings, safety, and maintainability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLP Essentials for Security: Language Meets Signals</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/nlp-essentials-for-security-language-meets-signals/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/nlp-essentials-for-security-language-meets-signals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how natural language processing connects text understanding with email and network signals to improve phishing detection, triage, and response in practical security workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Measure AI Impact in Operations?</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-do-you-measure-ai-impact-in-operations/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-do-you-measure-ai-impact-in-operations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to measure AI impact in operations using baselines, counterfactuals, quality metrics, and ROI models. Get practical methods for attribution, risk tracking, and scaling effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy and Control Checks Automated by AI in Finance</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/policy-and-control-checks-automated-by-ai-in-finance/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/policy-and-control-checks-automated-by-ai-in-finance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI automates finance policy and control checks with auditable rules, real-time validation, and risk scoring while preserving compliance and speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI in Retail: 12 Ways to Reimagine Merchandising</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-retail-12-ways-to-reimagine-merchandising/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-retail-12-ways-to-reimagine-merchandising/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover 12 practical ways generative AI reshapes retail merchandising, from product content and imagery to localization, assortment ideas, and governance workflows, with realistic examples and tradeoffs to guide adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-AI Collaboration in Learning: Where Each Excels</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/human-ai-collaboration-in-learning-where-each-excels/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/human-ai-collaboration-in-learning-where-each-excels/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See where human educators and AI each excel in learning, with concrete workflows for personalization, fair assessment, feedback quality, and academic integrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Distributed Ledger? Shared Records at Scale</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-distributed-ledger-shared-records-at-scale/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-distributed-ledger-shared-records-at-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how distributed ledgers maintain shared records at scale. Explore data structures, consensus, and the role of randomness for lotteries, leader election, and protocol fairness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Street Lighting System: Core Features Mapped</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-system-core-features-mapped/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-system-core-features-mapped/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Understand core features of an intelligent street lighting system, from sensors and dimming to control logic and data. Learn tradeoffs, decision criteria, and examples for safe, efficient roads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontier AI and Email Threats: Emerging Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/frontier-ai-and-email-threats-emerging-capabilities/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/frontier-ai-and-email-threats-emerging-capabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore how frontier AI reshapes email threat detection with generative risks, defense frameworks, and practical signals. Learn decision lenses, examples, and limits for safer deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Transforms Everyday Business Operations</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-ai-transforms-everyday-business-operations/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-ai-transforms-everyday-business-operations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See how the use of artificial intelligence in business reshapes operations, from service and finance to supply chain, with integration patterns, risk controls, and measurable impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning in Finance: 15 Examples That Deliver</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-finance-15-examples-that-deliver/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-finance-15-examples-that-deliver/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore 15 practical machine learning finance examples with controls, data needs, and tradeoffs. See where ML improves accuracy, speed, and auditability across core operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Online Shopping: What Works</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-online-shopping-what-works/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-online-shopping-what-works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn what truly works with artificial intelligence in online shopping, from definitions and decision frameworks to scenarios, tradeoffs, and next steps retailers can act on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for Student Assessment: Fair, Fast, and Actionable</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-student-assessment-fair-fast-and-actionable/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-student-assessment-fair-fast-and-actionable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to implement AI for student assessment that is fair, fast, and actionable. Set goals, structure evidence, build and validate models, and deliver feedback responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRF in Blockchains: Verifiable Randomness Explained</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vrf-in-blockchains-verifiable-randomness-explained/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vrf-in-blockchains-verifiable-randomness-explained/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how verifiable random functions bring unbiased, tamper-evident randomness to blockchains, powering fair lotteries, secure leader election, and protocol design without trusted coordinators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Street Light Control System: Setup and Tuning</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-light-control-system-setup-and-tuning/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-light-control-system-setup-and-tuning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Step by step how to plan, configure, validate, and refine an intelligent street light control system for safer roads and lower energy use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Threat Signals: AI Analytics Worth Tracking</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-threat-signals-ai-analytics-worth-tracking/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-threat-signals-ai-analytics-worth-tracking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover the email threat signals that matter for AI analytics, from authentication integrity to URLs, language intent, sender behavior, and attachments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Applications of AI: Where Value Comes First</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/business-applications-of-ai-where-value-comes-first/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/business-applications-of-ai-where-value-comes-first/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn where the business application of AI delivers measurable value, with patterns, integration paths, and metrics that translate ideas into outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPI Dashboard Automation with AI for CFO Teams</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/kpi-dashboard-automation-with-ai-for-cfo-teams/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/kpi-dashboard-automation-with-ai-for-cfo-teams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how CFO teams automate KPI dashboards with AI, from data mapping and governance to refresh pipelines, validation, and ongoing optimization with clear controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Trends in Retail: From Forecasting to Store Analytics</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-trends-in-retail-from-forecasting-to-store-analytics/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-trends-in-retail-from-forecasting-to-store-analytics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore seven AI trends reshaping retail, from demand forecasting and pricing to store analytics and workforce planning, with examples, tradeoffs, and practical next steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Machine Learning in Education: How They Differ</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-machine-learning-in-education-how-they-differ/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-machine-learning-in-education-how-they-differ/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn the difference between AI and machine learning in education, with practical examples for personalization, assessment, bias risks, governance, and implementation tradeoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Blockchain Network Types and How They Coordinate</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/top-blockchain-network-types-and-how-they-coordinate/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/top-blockchain-network-types-and-how-they-coordinate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore public, permissioned, and committee-based blockchain network types. Learn how consensus, randomness beacons, and VRFs coordinate fairness for lotteries and leader election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Street Lamp: Features, Aesthetics, and Siting</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lamp-features-aesthetics-and-siting/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lamp-features-aesthetics-and-siting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how intelligent street lamps blend features, aesthetics, and siting to improve safety and energy use while fitting local context. Get practical frameworks and examples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Phishing Detection with ML: Practical Steps</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-phishing-detection-with-ml-practical-steps/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-phishing-detection-with-ml-practical-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a clear path to build email phishing detection with machine learning. Plan data, engineer features, train, validate, and troubleshoot for reliable results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Solutions for Business: Choosing What Fits</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-solutions-for-business-choosing-what-fits/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-solutions-for-business-choosing-what-fits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare AI solutions for business across build vs buy, integration patterns, governance, and measurement. Learn criteria, tradeoffs, and example workflows to make confident decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDP vs RPA for Finance Document Workflows: Which Fits?</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/idp-vs-rpa-for-finance-document-workflows-which-fits/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/idp-vs-rpa-for-finance-document-workflows-which-fits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare IDP and RPA for finance document workflows across accuracy, controls, cost, and scale. Learn when each approach fits and how to mix them safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Retail Market: Growth Drivers, Segments, Outlook</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-market-growth-drivers-segments-outlook/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-market-growth-drivers-segments-outlook/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Understand the AI in retail market with clear growth drivers, key segments, and outlook. Learn decision lenses, practical scenarios, and risks to guide strategy for merchandising and operations leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Academic Integrity: Safeguards and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-academic-integrity-safeguards-and-strategies/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-academic-integrity-safeguards-and-strategies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare safeguards that protect academic integrity with AI. Learn how assessment design, proctoring models, data governance, and human review work together to deter misconduct and support fair learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomness Beacons Explained: Fairness You Can Verify</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/randomness-beacons-explained-fairness-you-can-verify/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/randomness-beacons-explained-fairness-you-can-verify/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how randomness beacons, entropy, and verifiable random functions deliver unbiased choices on blockchains for lotteries, leader election, and fair protocols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Dimming Schedules for Smart Street Lights</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-set-dimming-schedules-for-smart-street-lights/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-set-dimming-schedules-for-smart-street-lights/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, configure, and verify dimming schedules for smart street lights with practical steps, safe ranges, and fixes for common issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing Phishing Classifiers with AI: Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/developing-phishing-classifiers-with-ai-best-practices/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/developing-phishing-classifiers-with-ai-best-practices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, build, validate, and optimize AI phishing classifiers with clear steps, evaluation methods, defenses against evasion, and reproducible tooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Platforms for Business: Capabilities and Tradeoffs</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-platforms-for-business-capabilities-and-tradeoffs/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-platforms-for-business-capabilities-and-tradeoffs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare AI platforms for business across integration, data control, security, cost, and governance. Learn selection criteria, deployment paths, and tradeoffs that shape impact and risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expense Report Automation Using AI: Accuracy and Control</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/expense-report-automation-using-ai-accuracy-and-control/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/expense-report-automation-using-ai-accuracy-and-control/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to automate expense reports with AI, from data capture to policy checks and approvals, while preserving accuracy, audit trails, and finance controls with measurable results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Retail Industry: What’s Changing and Why Now</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-industry-whats-changing-and-why-now/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-industry-whats-changing-and-why-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI is reshaping the retail industry, from demand sensing to personalization. Understand strategic tradeoffs, governance, and value paths retailers can trust right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Learning with AI: Build Paths That Evolve</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/adaptive-learning-with-ai-build-paths-that-evolve/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/adaptive-learning-with-ai-build-paths-that-evolve/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design adaptive learning with AI through concrete steps. Map goals, select signals, set mastery thresholds, orchestrate content, and monitor fairness with transparent rules and human oversight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-Chain Randomness Security: Oracles, VRFs, and Risks</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/on-chain-randomness-security-oracles-vrfs-and-risks/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/on-chain-randomness-security-oracles-vrfs-and-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare oracle feeds, VRFs, and in-protocol randomness for secure lotteries and leader election. See attack surfaces, bias risks, and practical mitigations that protect on-chain fairness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Street Lighting System: Build, Test, Optimize</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-street-lighting-system-build-test-optimize/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-street-lighting-system-build-test-optimize/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, configure, and validate an automatic street lighting system with sensors, schedules, and tuning. Follow clear steps, tests, and fixes to balance savings and safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Malicious Attachments with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/detecting-malicious-attachments-with-deep-learning/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/detecting-malicious-attachments-with-deep-learning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how deep learning analyzes email attachments safely, from byte-level models to evaluation benchmarks, with tradeoffs for speed, accuracy, and deployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Business: 40 Examples That Deliver Results</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-business-40-examples-that-deliver-results/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-business-40-examples-that-deliver-results/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore 40 proven AI in business examples across sales, service, operations, HR, and finance. Learn impact ranges, integration tips, and governance guardrails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Automation in Finance with AI: Build It Right</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/document-automation-in-finance-with-ai-build-it-right/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/document-automation-in-finance-with-ai-build-it-right/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design, deploy, and validate AI-driven document automation for finance with controls, auditable workflows, and measurable accuracy improvements across invoices, expenses, and reconciliations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Retail Examples: 20 Initiatives Delivering ROI</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-examples-20-initiatives-delivering-roi/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-examples-20-initiatives-delivering-roi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See 20 practical AI in retail examples delivering measurable ROI. Learn where to start, what data matters, and pitfalls to avoid across merchandising and operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy Sources in Blockchain: Gathering True Random</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/entropy-sources-in-blockchain-gathering-true-random/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/entropy-sources-in-blockchain-gathering-true-random/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to gather, mix, and verify entropy sources in blockchain systems using VRFs, beacons, and commit reveal to secure lotteries, leader selection, and fair protocol outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Contracts in Insurance: Models and Trade‑offs</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-contracts-in-insurance-models-and-trade-offs/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-contracts-in-insurance-models-and-trade-offs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare smart contract models for insurance, from parametric payouts to automated escrow. Learn data, oracle, privacy, and governance trade-offs to design safe, compliant deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Smart Street Light: Design and Field Tips</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-smart-street-light-design-and-field-tips/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-smart-street-light-design-and-field-tips/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design automatic smart street lights that balance safety, savings, and maintainability with clear frameworks, examples, and field-ready decision criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Phishing URL Classification Model in Steps</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-a-phishing-url-classification-model-in-steps/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-a-phishing-url-classification-model-in-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a practical workflow to design, train, and deploy a phishing URL classification model, with features, metrics, validation, and safe troubleshooting guidance.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>