<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PulseGeek</title>
    <link>https://pulsegeek.com</link>
    <description>Tech news, gaming, and geek culture in one pulse</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <generator>PulseGeek Rss Feed Generator</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pulsegeek.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Is NLP for Email Security? A Practical Primer</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-nlp-for-email-security-a-practical-primer/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-nlp-for-email-security-a-practical-primer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how NLP improves email security with content and URL analysis, evaluation methods, and practical implementation patterns. Compare fit, limits, and validation tips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using AI for Business: Start Small, Measure, Expand</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/using-ai-for-business-start-small-measure-expand/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/using-ai-for-business-start-small-measure-expand/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to use AI for business with a stepwise playbook. Pick one use case, set a baseline, pilot safely, measure outcomes, and scale what works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Financial Forecasting &amp; FP&amp;A: Methods, Controls, ROI</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-forecasting-and-fpa-methods-controls-roi/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-financial-forecasting-and-fpa-methods-controls-roi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A practitioner guide to AI financial forecasting for FP&amp;A. Learn methods, controls, workflows, pitfalls, and how to size ROI with data-driven decisions and governance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retailers Using AI: Who’s Leading and What They Do</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retailers-using-ai-whos-leading-and-what-they-do/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retailers-using-ai-whos-leading-and-what-they-do/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See how leading retailers use AI across pricing, forecasting, personalization, and store operations, with concrete examples, patterns to copy, and practical tradeoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLONK ZK Proof: From Arithmetization to Verification</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plonk-zk-proof-from-arithmetization-to-verification/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plonk-zk-proof-from-arithmetization-to-verification/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how a PLONK zk proof is built end to end. Map logic to circuits, encode constraints as polynomials, and walk through proving and verification steps with practical tips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Street Light Control: Methods, Modes, and Triggers</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-methods-modes-and-triggers/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-methods-modes-and-triggers/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn smart street light control methods, operating modes, and sensor triggers with decision lenses, scenarios, and tradeoffs that balance safety, savings, and maintainability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Classification Techniques for Phishing Emails</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/text-classification-techniques-for-phishing-emails/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/text-classification-techniques-for-phishing-emails/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore eleven proven text classification techniques for phishing emails, with examples, tradeoffs, and practical guidance for reliable detection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating AI into Business Systems Without Disruption</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/integrating-ai-into-business-systems-without-disruption/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/integrating-ai-into-business-systems-without-disruption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a stepwise path for integrating AI into business systems without downtime. Scope seams, define data contracts, build safe APIs, and scale with canaries and measurable ROI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Intelligent Document Processing for Finance?</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-intelligent-document-processing-for-finance/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-intelligent-document-processing-for-finance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how intelligent document processing streamlines finance workflows by extracting, validating, and routing invoices, receipts, and statements with controls that satisfy audit, risk, and data quality needs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail AI Software Comparison: Platforms and Fit</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-ai-software-comparison-platforms-and-fit/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/retail-ai-software-comparison-platforms-and-fit/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare retail AI software types with clear criteria, tradeoffs, and scenarios. Learn where platforms, point solutions, or cloud services best fit and why.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mina Protocol: A Tiny Blockchain with Big ZK Ideas</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-protocol-a-tiny-blockchain-with-big-zk-ideas/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-protocol-a-tiny-blockchain-with-big-zk-ideas/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how Mina Protocol keeps the chain light with recursive proofs, enabling privacy and compression through zero-knowledge while preserving decentralization and practical verification on everyday devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart LED Street Lighting: 9 Options Cities Evaluate</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-led-street-lighting-9-options-cities-evaluate/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-led-street-lighting-9-options-cities-evaluate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore nine smart LED street lighting options cities compare, with examples, tradeoffs, and configuration tips to balance safety, savings, and maintainability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spear Phishing Detection: AI Features That Matter</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/spear-phishing-detection-ai-features-that-matter/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/spear-phishing-detection-ai-features-that-matter/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover spear phishing detection features that matter for AI models, with concrete examples, tradeoffs, and practical signals spanning content, sender, headers, URLs, and behavior.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing AI in Business: A Step-by-Step Playbook</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/implementing-ai-in-business-a-step-by-step-playbook/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/implementing-ai-in-business-a-step-by-step-playbook/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a practical playbook for implementing AI in business. Identify high-value use cases, assess data and risk, integrate solutions, run pilots, measure impact, and scale responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vendor Invoice Matching with ML: Reduce Exceptions Fast</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vendor-invoice-matching-with-ml-reduce-exceptions-fast/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vendor-invoice-matching-with-ml-reduce-exceptions-fast/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to implement machine learning for vendor invoice matching in accounting. Plan data, configure models, validate results, and reduce exceptions with controls and auditability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plan AI Projects in Retail Operations: Roadmaps That Work</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plan-ai-projects-in-retail-operations-roadmaps-that-work/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/plan-ai-projects-in-retail-operations-roadmaps-that-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan AI projects in retail operations with a proven roadmap. Scope problems, ready data, execute pilots, validate results, and scale responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of AI in Learning: Adaptive, Fair, and Trusted</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-future-of-ai-in-learning-adaptive-fair-and-trusted/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/the-future-of-ai-in-learning-adaptive-fair-and-trusted/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore the future of AI in learning with adaptive paths, fair assessment, and integrity safeguards, plus clear ties to machine learning concepts and practical rollout steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mina Crypto: 9 Reasons ZK Natives Are Watching</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-crypto-9-reasons-zk-natives-are-watching/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/mina-crypto-9-reasons-zk-natives-are-watching/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore why ZK builders track Mina crypto. Learn how a tiny chain, recursive proofs, and private zkApps enable verifiable compute, light clients, and practical privacy tradeoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensor Street Lamp: Choosing Motion, Ambient, and Radar</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/sensor-street-lamp-choosing-motion-ambient-and-radar/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/sensor-street-lamp-choosing-motion-ambient-and-radar/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to choose motion, ambient light, and radar sensors for street lamps, including placement rules, tuning ranges, and control logic tradeoffs for safety and savings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Artificial Intelligence in Email Security</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/open-artificial-intelligence-in-email-security/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/open-artificial-intelligence-in-email-security/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how open artificial intelligence advances email security using transparent models, evaluable features, and interoperable tooling, with tradeoffs around data privacy, robustness, and governance in production.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Implement AI in Business: A Practical Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-implement-ai-in-business-a-practical-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-implement-ai-in-business-a-practical-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to implement AI in business with a practical roadmap that selects the right use cases, integrates responsibly, measures outcomes, and scales value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use AI for Account Reconciliation: A Practical Blueprint</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/use-ai-for-account-reconciliation-a-practical-blueprint/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/use-ai-for-account-reconciliation-a-practical-blueprint/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn a step-by-step method to use AI for account reconciliation, from planning and data prep to matching logic, validation, and controls, with examples and troubleshooting tips for finance teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Is AI Used in Retail Merchandising? A Practical Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-is-ai-used-in-retail-merchandising-a-practical-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-is-ai-used-in-retail-merchandising-a-practical-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to apply AI in retail merchandising with clear steps, setup tips, validation methods, and fixes. Plan your use cases, prepare data, run experiments, and measure results responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalized Learning with AI: Design Blueprints That Work</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/personalized-learning-with-ai-design-blueprints-that-work/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/personalized-learning-with-ai-design-blueprints-that-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn a practical blueprint for personalized learning with AI. Define outcomes and signals, build adaptive paths, design fair assessments, and measure impact while safeguarding privacy and academic integrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-Knowledge Proofs: Privacy and Proof Without Sharing</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zero-knowledge-proofs-privacy-and-proof-without-sharing/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/zero-knowledge-proofs-privacy-and-proof-without-sharing/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how zero knowledge proofs deliver privacy and compression by proving facts without revealing data, and see where SNARKs, STARKs, and rollups fit. Practical guidance, choices, and pitfalls for builders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Wireless Street Lighting Systems: Key Choices</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-wireless-street-lighting-systems-key-choices/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-wireless-street-lighting-systems-key-choices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how intelligent wireless street lighting systems work, key design tradeoffs, sensor choices, and control strategies to balance savings, safety, and maintainability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLP Essentials for Security: Language Meets Signals</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/nlp-essentials-for-security-language-meets-signals/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/nlp-essentials-for-security-language-meets-signals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how natural language processing connects text understanding with email and network signals to improve phishing detection, triage, and response in practical security workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Measure AI Impact in Operations?</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-do-you-measure-ai-impact-in-operations/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-do-you-measure-ai-impact-in-operations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to measure AI impact in operations using baselines, counterfactuals, quality metrics, and ROI models. Get practical methods for attribution, risk tracking, and scaling effects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy and Control Checks Automated by AI in Finance</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/policy-and-control-checks-automated-by-ai-in-finance/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/policy-and-control-checks-automated-by-ai-in-finance/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI automates finance policy and control checks with auditable rules, real-time validation, and risk scoring while preserving compliance and speed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI in Retail: 12 Ways to Reimagine Merchandising</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-retail-12-ways-to-reimagine-merchandising/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-retail-12-ways-to-reimagine-merchandising/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover 12 practical ways generative AI reshapes retail merchandising, from product content and imagery to localization, assortment ideas, and governance workflows, with realistic examples and tradeoffs to guide adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human-AI Collaboration in Learning: Where Each Excels</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/human-ai-collaboration-in-learning-where-each-excels/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/human-ai-collaboration-in-learning-where-each-excels/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See where human educators and AI each excel in learning, with concrete workflows for personalization, fair assessment, feedback quality, and academic integrity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Distributed Ledger? Shared Records at Scale</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-distributed-ledger-shared-records-at-scale/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-distributed-ledger-shared-records-at-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how distributed ledgers maintain shared records at scale. Explore data structures, consensus, and the role of randomness for lotteries, leader election, and protocol fairness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Street Lighting System: Core Features Mapped</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-system-core-features-mapped/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-system-core-features-mapped/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Understand core features of an intelligent street lighting system, from sensors and dimming to control logic and data. Learn tradeoffs, decision criteria, and examples for safe, efficient roads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontier AI and Email Threats: Emerging Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/frontier-ai-and-email-threats-emerging-capabilities/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/frontier-ai-and-email-threats-emerging-capabilities/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore how frontier AI reshapes email threat detection with generative risks, defense frameworks, and practical signals. Learn decision lenses, examples, and limits for safer deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Transforms Everyday Business Operations</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-ai-transforms-everyday-business-operations/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-ai-transforms-everyday-business-operations/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See how the use of artificial intelligence in business reshapes operations, from service and finance to supply chain, with integration patterns, risk controls, and measurable impact.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning in Finance: 15 Examples That Deliver</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-finance-15-examples-that-deliver/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-finance-15-examples-that-deliver/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore 15 practical machine learning finance examples with controls, data needs, and tradeoffs. See where ML improves accuracy, speed, and auditability across core operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Online Shopping: What Works</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-online-shopping-what-works/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-online-shopping-what-works/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn what truly works with artificial intelligence in online shopping, from definitions and decision frameworks to scenarios, tradeoffs, and next steps retailers can act on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for Student Assessment: Fair, Fast, and Actionable</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-student-assessment-fair-fast-and-actionable/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-student-assessment-fair-fast-and-actionable/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to implement AI for student assessment that is fair, fast, and actionable. Set goals, structure evidence, build and validate models, and deliver feedback responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VRF in Blockchains: Verifiable Randomness Explained</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vrf-in-blockchains-verifiable-randomness-explained/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/vrf-in-blockchains-verifiable-randomness-explained/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how verifiable random functions bring unbiased, tamper-evident randomness to blockchains, powering fair lotteries, secure leader election, and protocol design without trusted coordinators.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Street Light Control System: Setup and Tuning</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-light-control-system-setup-and-tuning/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-light-control-system-setup-and-tuning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Step by step how to plan, configure, validate, and refine an intelligent street light control system for safer roads and lower energy use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Threat Signals: AI Analytics Worth Tracking</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-threat-signals-ai-analytics-worth-tracking/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-threat-signals-ai-analytics-worth-tracking/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover the email threat signals that matter for AI analytics, from authentication integrity to URLs, language intent, sender behavior, and attachments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Applications of AI: Where Value Comes First</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/business-applications-of-ai-where-value-comes-first/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/business-applications-of-ai-where-value-comes-first/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn where the business application of AI delivers measurable value, with patterns, integration paths, and metrics that translate ideas into outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KPI Dashboard Automation with AI for CFO Teams</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/kpi-dashboard-automation-with-ai-for-cfo-teams/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/kpi-dashboard-automation-with-ai-for-cfo-teams/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how CFO teams automate KPI dashboards with AI, from data mapping and governance to refresh pipelines, validation, and ongoing optimization with clear controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Trends in Retail: From Forecasting to Store Analytics</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-trends-in-retail-from-forecasting-to-store-analytics/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-trends-in-retail-from-forecasting-to-store-analytics/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore seven AI trends reshaping retail, from demand forecasting and pricing to store analytics and workforce planning, with examples, tradeoffs, and practical next steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Machine Learning in Education: How They Differ</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-machine-learning-in-education-how-they-differ/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-machine-learning-in-education-how-they-differ/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn the difference between AI and machine learning in education, with practical examples for personalization, assessment, bias risks, governance, and implementation tradeoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Blockchain Network Types and How They Coordinate</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/top-blockchain-network-types-and-how-they-coordinate/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/top-blockchain-network-types-and-how-they-coordinate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore public, permissioned, and committee-based blockchain network types. Learn how consensus, randomness beacons, and VRFs coordinate fairness for lotteries and leader election.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Street Lamp: Features, Aesthetics, and Siting</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lamp-features-aesthetics-and-siting/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lamp-features-aesthetics-and-siting/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how intelligent street lamps blend features, aesthetics, and siting to improve safety and energy use while fitting local context. Get practical frameworks and examples.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Phishing Detection with ML: Practical Steps</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-phishing-detection-with-ml-practical-steps/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-phishing-detection-with-ml-practical-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a clear path to build email phishing detection with machine learning. Plan data, engineer features, train, validate, and troubleshoot for reliable results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Solutions for Business: Choosing What Fits</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-solutions-for-business-choosing-what-fits/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-solutions-for-business-choosing-what-fits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare AI solutions for business across build vs buy, integration patterns, governance, and measurement. Learn criteria, tradeoffs, and example workflows to make confident decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDP vs RPA for Finance Document Workflows: Which Fits?</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/idp-vs-rpa-for-finance-document-workflows-which-fits/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/idp-vs-rpa-for-finance-document-workflows-which-fits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare IDP and RPA for finance document workflows across accuracy, controls, cost, and scale. Learn when each approach fits and how to mix them safely.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>