<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PulseGeek</title>
    <link>https://pulsegeek.com</link>
    <description>Tech news, gaming, and geek culture in one pulse</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <generator>PulseGeek Rss Feed Generator</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pulsegeek.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Email Phishing Detection with ML: Practical Steps</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-phishing-detection-with-ml-practical-steps/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/email-phishing-detection-with-ml-practical-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a clear path to build email phishing detection with machine learning. Plan data, engineer features, train, validate, and troubleshoot for reliable results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Solutions for Business: Choosing What Fits</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-solutions-for-business-choosing-what-fits/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-solutions-for-business-choosing-what-fits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare AI solutions for business across build vs buy, integration patterns, governance, and measurement. Learn criteria, tradeoffs, and example workflows to make confident decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDP vs RPA for Finance Document Workflows: Which Fits?</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/idp-vs-rpa-for-finance-document-workflows-which-fits/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/idp-vs-rpa-for-finance-document-workflows-which-fits/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare IDP and RPA for finance document workflows across accuracy, controls, cost, and scale. Learn when each approach fits and how to mix them safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Retail Market: Growth Drivers, Segments, Outlook</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-market-growth-drivers-segments-outlook/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-market-growth-drivers-segments-outlook/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Understand the AI in retail market with clear growth drivers, key segments, and outlook. Learn decision lenses, practical scenarios, and risks to guide strategy for merchandising and operations leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Academic Integrity: Safeguards and Strategies</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-academic-integrity-safeguards-and-strategies/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-and-academic-integrity-safeguards-and-strategies/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare safeguards that protect academic integrity with AI. Learn how assessment design, proctoring models, data governance, and human review work together to deter misconduct and support fair learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Randomness Beacons Explained: Fairness You Can Verify</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/randomness-beacons-explained-fairness-you-can-verify/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/randomness-beacons-explained-fairness-you-can-verify/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how randomness beacons, entropy, and verifiable random functions deliver unbiased choices on blockchains for lotteries, leader election, and fair protocols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Dimming Schedules for Smart Street Lights</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-set-dimming-schedules-for-smart-street-lights/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-set-dimming-schedules-for-smart-street-lights/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, configure, and verify dimming schedules for smart street lights with practical steps, safe ranges, and fixes for common issues.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing Phishing Classifiers with AI: Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/developing-phishing-classifiers-with-ai-best-practices/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/developing-phishing-classifiers-with-ai-best-practices/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, build, validate, and optimize AI phishing classifiers with clear steps, evaluation methods, defenses against evasion, and reproducible tooling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Platforms for Business: Capabilities and Tradeoffs</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-platforms-for-business-capabilities-and-tradeoffs/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-platforms-for-business-capabilities-and-tradeoffs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare AI platforms for business across integration, data control, security, cost, and governance. Learn selection criteria, deployment paths, and tradeoffs that shape impact and risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expense Report Automation Using AI: Accuracy and Control</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/expense-report-automation-using-ai-accuracy-and-control/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/expense-report-automation-using-ai-accuracy-and-control/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to automate expense reports with AI, from data capture to policy checks and approvals, while preserving accuracy, audit trails, and finance controls with measurable results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Retail Industry: What’s Changing and Why Now</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-industry-whats-changing-and-why-now/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-retail-industry-whats-changing-and-why-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI is reshaping the retail industry, from demand sensing to personalization. Understand strategic tradeoffs, governance, and value paths retailers can trust right now.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Learning with AI: Build Paths That Evolve</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/adaptive-learning-with-ai-build-paths-that-evolve/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/adaptive-learning-with-ai-build-paths-that-evolve/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design adaptive learning with AI through concrete steps. Map goals, select signals, set mastery thresholds, orchestrate content, and monitor fairness with transparent rules and human oversight.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-Chain Randomness Security: Oracles, VRFs, and Risks</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/on-chain-randomness-security-oracles-vrfs-and-risks/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/on-chain-randomness-security-oracles-vrfs-and-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare oracle feeds, VRFs, and in-protocol randomness for secure lotteries and leader election. See attack surfaces, bias risks, and practical mitigations that protect on-chain fairness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Street Lighting System: Build, Test, Optimize</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-street-lighting-system-build-test-optimize/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-street-lighting-system-build-test-optimize/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, configure, and validate an automatic street lighting system with sensors, schedules, and tuning. Follow clear steps, tests, and fixes to balance savings and safety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Malicious Attachments with Deep Learning</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/detecting-malicious-attachments-with-deep-learning/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/detecting-malicious-attachments-with-deep-learning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how deep learning analyzes email attachments safely, from byte-level models to evaluation benchmarks, with tradeoffs for speed, accuracy, and deployment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Business: 40 Examples That Deliver Results</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-business-40-examples-that-deliver-results/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-business-40-examples-that-deliver-results/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore 40 practical AI in business examples across customer experience, marketing, finance, supply chain, and back office. Learn tradeoffs, integration tips, and how to measure results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Document Automation in Finance with AI: Build It Right</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/document-automation-in-finance-with-ai-build-it-right/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/document-automation-in-finance-with-ai-build-it-right/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design, deploy, and validate AI-driven document automation for finance with controls, auditable workflows, and measurable accuracy improvements across invoices, expenses, and reconciliations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Retail Examples: 20 Initiatives Delivering ROI</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-examples-20-initiatives-delivering-roi/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-examples-20-initiatives-delivering-roi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See 20 practical AI in retail examples delivering measurable ROI. Learn where to start, what data matters, and pitfalls to avoid across merchandising and operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Entropy Sources in Blockchain: Gathering True Random</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/entropy-sources-in-blockchain-gathering-true-random/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/entropy-sources-in-blockchain-gathering-true-random/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to gather, mix, and verify entropy sources in blockchain systems using VRFs, beacons, and commit reveal to secure lotteries, leader selection, and fair protocol outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Contracts in Insurance: Models and Trade‑offs</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-contracts-in-insurance-models-and-trade-offs/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-contracts-in-insurance-models-and-trade-offs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare smart contract models for insurance, from parametric payouts to automated escrow. Learn data, oracle, privacy, and governance trade-offs to design safe, compliant deployments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Smart Street Light: Design and Field Tips</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-smart-street-light-design-and-field-tips/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automatic-smart-street-light-design-and-field-tips/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design automatic smart street lights that balance safety, savings, and maintainability with clear frameworks, examples, and field-ready decision criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Phishing URL Classification Model in Steps</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-a-phishing-url-classification-model-in-steps/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-a-phishing-url-classification-model-in-steps/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a practical workflow to design, train, and deploy a phishing URL classification model, with features, metrics, validation, and safe troubleshooting guidance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Business Processes: Mapping Value to Workflow</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-business-processes-mapping-value-to-workflow/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-business-processes-mapping-value-to-workflow/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to map AI to business processes, pick high‑impact workflows, choose integration patterns, set baselines, and measure outcomes. Includes governance guardrails and a simple routing pattern to scale safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversational AI in Finance: Assistants That Actually Help</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/conversational-ai-in-finance-assistants-that-actually-help/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/conversational-ai-in-finance-assistants-that-actually-help/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how conversational AI streamlines finance work with safe approvals, reconciliations, and document queries, while preserving controls, audit trails, and data integrity across ERP and reporting workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Retail Case Study Examples: Lessons and Results</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-case-study-examples-lessons-and-results/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-case-study-examples-lessons-and-results/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore seven concrete AI in retail case study examples with tactics, measurable outcomes, and tradeoffs so merchandisers and operators can act with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI in Education: Content, Feedback, and Risks</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-education-content-feedback-and-risks/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-education-content-feedback-and-risks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how generative AI can support lesson content and actionable feedback in education while managing privacy, bias, and accuracy risks with practical safeguards and workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Random Number Generation on Blockchains: Secure Methods</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/random-number-generation-on-blockchains-secure-methods/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/random-number-generation-on-blockchains-secure-methods/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn secure random number generation in blockchain systems, from entropy and commit reveal to VRFs and randomness beacons, with design patterns for lotteries, leader election, and fair protocols.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Contracts for Real Estate: From Escrow to Title</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-contracts-for-real-estate-from-escrow-to-title/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-contracts-for-real-estate-from-escrow-to-title/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Build a practical workflow for smart contracts in real estate. Map escrow conditions, wire data safely, deploy a minimal contract, and manage title releases with clear checks, audits, and jurisdiction-aware risk controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated Street Lighting: Strategies for Always-Right Light</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automated-street-lighting-strategies-for-always-right-light/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automated-street-lighting-strategies-for-always-right-light/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how automated street lighting works, compare control strategies, and apply decision lenses for safe visibility, energy savings, and regulatory compliance in real streets.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Data Science for Phishing Detection: Step by Step</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-science-for-phishing-detection-step-by-step/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-science-for-phishing-detection-step-by-step/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, build, validate, and improve an AI data science workflow for phishing detection with clear steps, metrics, and safeguards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for Business Operations: Efficiency That Compounds</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-operations-efficiency-that-compounds/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-operations-efficiency-that-compounds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to apply AI for business operations with clear use cases, integration options, and metrics that compound efficiency while managing risk and governance across teams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automate Invoice Processing with AI: From Inbox to ERP</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automate-invoice-processing-with-ai-from-inbox-to-erp/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/automate-invoice-processing-with-ai-from-inbox-to-erp/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to automate invoice processing with AI, from email intake to ERP posting, including data capture, validation, approvals, audit trails, and error handling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Retail Business: Strategy to Pilot to Scale</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-business-strategy-to-pilot-to-scale/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-business-strategy-to-pilot-to-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how retailers translate AI strategy into pilots and scale. Define value, choose data, pick sponsors, de-risk delivery, and govern models for durable results across merchandising, operations, and customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Privacy for AI in Education: Questions Answered</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/data-privacy-for-ai-in-education-questions-answered/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/data-privacy-for-ai-in-education-questions-answered/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Get clear answers on data privacy for AI in education. Learn what counts as student data, how to vet tools, set retention rules, and build safeguards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Merkle Proofs Matter: Lightweight Trust at Scale</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/why-merkle-proofs-matter-lightweight-trust-at-scale/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/why-merkle-proofs-matter-lightweight-trust-at-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how Merkle proofs deliver compact verification for blocks and state. See how SPV clients, headers, and Patricia tries enable trust-minimized checks at network scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain and Supply Chain: Traceability in Action</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/blockchain-and-supply-chain-traceability-in-action/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/blockchain-and-supply-chain-traceability-in-action/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See how blockchain sharpens supply chain traceability with verifiable events, automated compliance, and finance tied to real movement. Practical steps, code, and tradeoffs for pilots that scale.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Street Light Control Systems: A Practical Configuration Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-systems-a-practical-configuration-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-light-control-systems-a-practical-configuration-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, configure, and tune smart street light control systems. Compare sensor options, dimming profiles, and automation strategies for safe, efficient public lighting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Applications in Email Security: Patterns That Work</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-applications-in-email-security-patterns-that-work/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-applications-in-email-security-patterns-that-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore proven AI applications in email security. Learn patterns for headers, URLs, content, attachments, graphs, reinforcement signals, and ensembles, with tradeoffs and real-world implementation tips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Business Process Automation: Design, Pilot, Scale</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-process-automation-design-pilot-scale/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-process-automation-design-pilot-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design, pilot, and scale AI business process automation with measurable impact. Use a stepwise method for use case selection, data readiness, integration, and governance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Financial Sector: Operations at Scale</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-financial-sector-operations-at-scale/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-financial-sector-operations-at-scale/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI transforms financial sector operations with audit-ready automation, data controls, and decision frameworks to prioritize use cases, manage risks, and scale responsibly across core workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Retail and E‑Commerce: 15 Real-World Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-and-e-commerce-15-real-world-use-cases/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-retail-and-e-commerce-15-real-world-use-cases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore 15 practical AI use cases in retail and e-commerce, with examples, data inputs, and tradeoffs to guide teams from idea to rollout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is the Mempool? Where Transactions Wait Their Turn</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-the-mempool-where-transactions-wait-their-turn/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-the-mempool-where-transactions-wait-their-turn/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how the mempool works, why transactions queue, and how fees, priority, and propagation shape confirmation. See how proofs and light clients verify data efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain and IoT: Devices That Verify and Cooperate</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/blockchain-and-iot-devices-that-verify-and-cooperate/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/blockchain-and-iot-devices-that-verify-and-cooperate/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore blockchain and IoT through practical smart contract use cases. See how devices attest data, trigger maintenance, enable metered billing, and coordinate fleets with verifiable trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Street Lighting: How It Works and Why It Matters</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-how-it-works-and-why-it-matters/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/intelligent-street-lighting-how-it-works-and-why-it-matters/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Understand intelligent street lighting from pole to cloud, including controls, networks, benefits, and operating models that scale from pilots to citywide reliability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phishing Defense with NLP: A Complete Build Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/phishing-defense-with-nlp-a-complete-build-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/phishing-defense-with-nlp-a-complete-build-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Build an NLP-driven phishing defense from principles to practice. Learn data choices, features, workflows, evaluation, and deployment patterns that reduce risk while balancing precision, recall, and operational cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Business Automation: From Manual to Autonomous</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-automation-from-manual-to-autonomous/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-automation-from-manual-to-autonomous/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A practical how-to for ai business automation. Map processes, set autonomy levels, build an orchestrator, add guardrails, and measure impact to scale confidently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Finance Department: Roles, Skills, and Wins</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-finance-department-roles-skills-and-wins/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-the-finance-department-roles-skills-and-wins/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI reshapes the finance department. Define practical roles, upskill critical abilities, pick the right use cases, and avoid common pitfalls while keeping controls, accuracy, and audit trails in focus.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Retail Strategy: Trends, Examples, and Execution Playbooks</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-retail-strategy-trends-examples-execution-playbooks/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-retail-strategy-trends-examples-execution-playbooks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 09:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI reshapes retail strategy with core concepts, proven examples, and practical execution playbooks that connect merchandising, pricing, and operations to measurable outcomes across channels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud AI for Education: Architecture, Costs, and Control</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/cloud-ai-for-education-architecture-costs-and-control/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/cloud-ai-for-education-architecture-costs-and-control/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Plan cloud AI for schools with a practical reference architecture, cost models, and governance controls that protect student data while scaling instruction and operations responsibly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Track a Transaction: Block Explorer Basics in Action</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/track-a-transaction-block-explorer-basics-in-action/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/track-a-transaction-block-explorer-basics-in-action/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to track a transaction with a block explorer, read fees and confirmations, and verify integrity using hashes, Merkle roots, and practical proof concepts.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>