<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PulseGeek</title>
    <link>https://pulsegeek.com</link>
    <description>Tech news, gaming, and geek culture in one pulse</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <generator>PulseGeek Rss Feed Generator</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:16:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pulsegeek.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Use AI for Network Anomaly Detection</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-use-ai-for-network-anomaly-detection/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-use-ai-for-network-anomaly-detection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn a practical path to build AI-driven network anomaly detection, from data planning and environment setup to execution, validation, and troubleshooting with measurable outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use AI for Small Business: Start and Succeed</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-use-ai-for-small-business-start-and-succeed/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-to-use-ai-for-small-business-start-and-succeed/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to use AI for small business with stepwise goals, affordable tools, prompt workflows, measurement, and risk guardrails that scale with your team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top AI Applications in Finance Teams Today</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/top-ai-applications-in-finance-teams-today/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/top-ai-applications-in-finance-teams-today/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore practical AI applications finance teams deploy now, from forecasting and anomaly detection to scenario planning and cash flow modeling, with controls and tradeoffs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Shopping AI: Capabilities, Use Cases, Adoption</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/google-shopping-ai-capabilities-use-cases-adoption/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/google-shopping-ai-capabilities-use-cases-adoption/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare Google Shopping AI with retailer-native AI and marketplaces. See strengths, limitations, and scenarios to guide adoption decisions and smarter investments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of Smart Street Lighting: Savings, Safety, Service</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/benefits-of-smart-street-lighting-savings-safety-service/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/benefits-of-smart-street-lighting-savings-safety-service/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore the biggest benefits of smart street lighting including measurable energy savings, improved safety, faster maintenance, and better city services with fewer disruptions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Is Used in Cyber Security: Practical Paths</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-ai-is-used-in-cyber-security-practical-paths/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/how-ai-is-used-in-cyber-security-practical-paths/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI is used in cyber security with clear definitions, selection frameworks, real examples, and limits so teams can evaluate detection and response paths with less risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best AI for Small Business: Tools That Punch Above</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/best-ai-for-small-business-tools-that-punch-above/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/best-ai-for-small-business-tools-that-punch-above/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare the best AI for small business across marketing, sales, operations, and support. See costs, fit, and rollout tips with practical examples and selection criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scenario Planning with AI for Budgeting: Step-by-Step</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/scenario-planning-with-ai-for-budgeting-step-by-step/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/scenario-planning-with-ai-for-budgeting-step-by-step/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to run AI-driven scenario planning for budgeting with clear steps, data prep, modeling, validation, and controls that finance teams can repeat and audit.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversational AI in Retail: Journeys That Convert</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/conversational-ai-in-retail-journeys-that-convert/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/conversational-ai-in-retail-journeys-that-convert/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how conversational AI reshapes retail journeys, from guided discovery to checkout. See decision lenses, scenarios, and tradeoffs that improve conversion and trust across channels.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Street Lighting: When, Where, and How to Use It</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/adaptive-street-lighting-when-where-and-how-to-use-it/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/adaptive-street-lighting-when-where-and-how-to-use-it/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn what adaptive street lighting is, when it makes sense, where it excels, and how to choose control strategies that balance safety, savings, and equity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep Learning for Network Anomalies: A Hands-on Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/deep-learning-for-network-anomalies-a-hands-on-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/deep-learning-for-network-anomalies-a-hands-on-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to plan, build, and validate deep learning anomaly detection for network traffic, from data prep to model tuning, metrics, and safe deployment with troubleshooting tips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Software for Small Business: Compare Smart Picks</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-software-for-small-business-compare-smart-picks/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-software-for-small-business-compare-smart-picks/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare AI software for small business by fit, cost, and ROI. See marketing, sales, operations, and support tools with selection criteria, security checks, and an adoption path to real outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning in Finance: Core Concepts and Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-finance-core-concepts-and-use-cases/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-in-finance-core-concepts-and-use-cases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how machine learning improves finance decisions with clear concepts, decision lenses, and realistic examples, plus common pitfalls and governance practices to reduce risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conversational AI for Retail: Design, Train, and Measure</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/conversational-ai-for-retail-design-train-and-measure/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/conversational-ai-for-retail-design-train-and-measure/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Build retail conversational AI that converts. Plan intents and guardrails, prepare data and tools, execute training, validate outcomes, and optimize with analytics and QA workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Smart City Lighting Solutions Cities Compare in 2025</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/7-smart-city-lighting-solutions-cities-compare-in-2025/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/7-smart-city-lighting-solutions-cities-compare-in-2025/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>See seven practical smart city lighting solutions cities compare in 2025, with examples, tradeoffs, and selection tips for safety, savings, and scalability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Choosing an AI System for Intrusion Detection</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/choosing-an-ai-system-for-intrusion-detection/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/choosing-an-ai-system-for-intrusion-detection/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Compare AI intrusion detection options by data coverage, accuracy, latency, explainability, integrations, and cost. Learn how to weigh tradeoffs and pick the right fit for your environment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Small Business: From Idea to Everyday Work</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-small-business-from-idea-to-everyday-work/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-small-business-from-idea-to-everyday-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how small businesses move from AI ideas to reliable daily workflows. Define outcomes, prep data, choose tools, build one process, and measure ROI with governance and guardrails.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Finance Applications: 20 Real Use Cases</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-finance-applications-20-real-use-cases/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/machine-learning-finance-applications-20-real-use-cases/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore 20 proven machine learning finance applications that improve forecasting, risk control, pricing, and working capital. Learn tradeoffs, governance tips, and when to choose simpler models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence Online Shopping: What Shoppers See</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-online-shopping-what-shoppers-see/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-online-shopping-what-shoppers-see/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Understand how artificial intelligence shapes online shopping across discovery, guidance, and checkout. Learn buyer-facing concepts, decision lenses, scenarios, and tradeoffs to design journeys shoppers trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 Advantages of a Smart Street Light System Explained</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/12-advantages-of-a-smart-street-light-system-explained/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/12-advantages-of-a-smart-street-light-system-explained/</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore twelve clear advantages of smart street light systems, with examples, tradeoffs, and decision cues for planners seeking energy savings, safety gains, and reliable service.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Machine Learning Intrusion Detection Pipeline</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-a-machine-learning-intrusion-detection-pipeline/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-a-machine-learning-intrusion-detection-pipeline/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to design and implement a machine learning intrusion detection pipeline with data prep, modeling, validation, and SOC integration steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for SMEs: Scale Capabilities Without Headcount</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-smes-scale-capabilities-without-headcount/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-smes-scale-capabilities-without-headcount/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI for SMEs expands capacity without new hires. Prioritize practical use cases, set up lean data workflows, control costs, and measure ROI with a staged adoption plan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve Forecast Accuracy with AI: Techniques That Work</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/improve-forecast-accuracy-with-ai-techniques-that-work/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/improve-forecast-accuracy-with-ai-techniques-that-work/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn a step-by-step path to boost forecast accuracy with AI in finance, from data design and model selection to validation, monitoring, and troubleshooting with measurable error reductions and clear controls.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Store AI: What’s Transferable to Your Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-store-ai-whats-transferable-to-your-roadmap/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-store-ai-whats-transferable-to-your-roadmap/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn which Amazon store AI practices can transfer to your retail roadmap, with clear definitions, decision lenses, examples, and tradeoffs to guide adoption.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Smart Street Lamps Worth Studying for Urban Upgrades</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/10-smart-street-lamps-worth-studying-for-urban-upgrades/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/10-smart-street-lamps-worth-studying-for-urban-upgrades/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore ten smart street lamp patterns, with examples, benefits, and tradeoffs for safety, energy, and maintenance. See where they fit, how they work, and what to watch in procurement and rollout.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence in Security: Core Concepts</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-security-core-concepts/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/artificial-intelligence-in-security-core-concepts/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn the core concepts of artificial intelligence in security, including detection signals, model choices, thresholds, evaluation, and human oversight to build reliable SOC analytics and resilient defenses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for Small Business Marketing: Tactics That Convert</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-small-business-marketing-tactics-that-convert/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-small-business-marketing-tactics-that-convert/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>A stepwise playbook for small business marketing with AI. Prioritize use cases, prepare data, run lean experiments, and measure lift to scale what converts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI in Finance: Use Cases, Limits, and Guardrails</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-finance-use-cases-limits-and-guardrails/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/generative-ai-in-finance-use-cases-limits-and-guardrails/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how generative AI fits finance workflows, with practical use cases, risk limits, and governance guardrails that preserve accuracy, compliance, and stakeholder trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Go AI: Tech Behind Just Walk Out Experiences</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-go-ai-tech-behind-just-walk-out-experiences/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-go-ai-tech-behind-just-walk-out-experiences/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore the technology powering Just Walk Out at Amazon Go, including sensor fusion, identity, and privacy safeguards, with decision frameworks and practical tradeoffs for retailers evaluating similar systems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smart Street Lighting: Citywide Benefits, Safety, and Design</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-citywide-benefits-safety-and-design/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/smart-street-lighting-citywide-benefits-safety-and-design/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Get a practitioner-grade overview of smart street lighting, covering citywide benefits, safety impacts, design choices, and integration with broader smart city programs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Driven SOC Analytics Techniques You Can Apply Now</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-driven-soc-analytics-techniques-you-can-apply-now/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-driven-soc-analytics-techniques-you-can-apply-now/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Practical SOC analytics techniques using AI to enrich telemetry, build behavior baselines, correlate signals, and close the loop with feedback. Learn tradeoffs, examples, and steps to apply safely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for Entrepreneurs: Leverage, Focus, and Momentum</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-entrepreneurs-leverage-focus-and-momentum/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-entrepreneurs-leverage-focus-and-momentum/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn practical ways entrepreneurs can use AI to create leverage, choose high impact workflows, pick sane tools, and build compounding momentum without overspending.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finance AI Explained: Data, Models, and Value Realization</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/finance-ai-explained-data-models-and-value-realization/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/finance-ai-explained-data-models-and-value-realization/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how finance AI turns raw data into useful models and measurable value. See definitions, decision frameworks, examples, risks, and steps to link analytics with controls and business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon AI Store: Lessons from Frictionless Shopping</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-store-lessons-from-frictionless-shopping/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-store-lessons-from-frictionless-shopping/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn practical lessons from frictionless shopping in Amazon-style AI stores. Understand definitions, decision lenses, and tradeoffs to evaluate readiness, reduce friction, and prioritize improvements without overspending on unproven technology.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wireless Street Light Control Systems: Topologies Compared</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/wireless-street-light-control-systems-topologies-compared/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/wireless-street-light-control-systems-topologies-compared/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how wireless street light control system topologies differ, when to choose each, and the tradeoffs in latency, resilience, cost, and operations for city‑scale lighting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Network Security Tools and Patterns to Know</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-network-security-tools-and-patterns-to-know/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-network-security-tools-and-patterns-to-know/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore seven AI network security tools and patterns with examples, tradeoffs, and deployment tips for SOC analytics, anomaly detection, and resilient operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for Business Growth: A Roadmap to Compounding ROI</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-growth-a-roadmap-to-compounding-roi/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-growth-a-roadmap-to-compounding-roi/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to use AI for business growth with a practical roadmap. Prioritize use cases, prep data, run measurable pilots, and scale wins for compounding ROI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explainable AI in Finance: Transparency Without Tradeoffs</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/explainable-ai-in-finance-transparency-without-tradeoffs/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/explainable-ai-in-finance-transparency-without-tradeoffs/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how explainable AI brings clarity to finance models, balances risk and accuracy, and fits controls. Explore methods like SHAP, monotonicity, and surrogate models with practical decision criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon AI Grocery Store: Inventory, Vision, Checkout</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-grocery-store-inventory-vision-checkout/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/amazon-ai-grocery-store-inventory-vision-checkout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI powers grocery inventory accuracy, computer vision for shelf insight, and low-friction checkout. See frameworks, scenarios, tradeoffs, and pragmatic guardrails that retailers can apply without copying any one vendor’s blueprint.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is a Street Light Dimming Profile? A Simple Explainer</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-street-light-dimming-profile-a-simple-explainer/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/what-is-a-street-light-dimming-profile-a-simple-explainer/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn what a street light dimming profile is, how it balances safety and savings, when to use it, and how to configure and verify schedules with sensors, rules, and real‑world constraints.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Cyber Security: Threat Models and Tuning</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-cyber-security-threat-models-and-tuning/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-cyber-security-threat-models-and-tuning/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how to define practical threat models for AI in cyber security and tune detection systems with measurable criteria, guardrails, and risk-based decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI for Business Development: Open More Right Doors</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-development-open-more-right-doors/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-for-business-development-open-more-right-doors/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover practical ways to use AI for business development. Learn ICP definition, data readiness, workflow design, scoring models, and outreach tactics that focus efforts and improve conversion with measurable results.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build AI Forecasting Models for FP&amp;A: A Technical Guide</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-ai-forecasting-models-for-fpa-a-technical-guide/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/build-ai-forecasting-models-for-fpa-a-technical-guide/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Follow a practical, step by step path to design, train, and validate AI forecasting models for FP&amp;A with controls, metrics, and troubleshooting tips that protect accuracy and trust.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Shopping: Guided Discovery and Confidence Cues</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-shopping-guided-discovery-and-confidence-cues/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-shopping-guided-discovery-and-confidence-cues/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI guides shopping discovery and builds confidence through intent signals, conversational helpers, and transparent cues that reduce friction and boost conversion.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Lighting Control System: Architecture and Options</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-lighting-control-system-architecture-and-options/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-lighting-control-system-architecture-and-options/</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how a street lighting control system is architected, key options from nodes to networks, and decision factors that balance savings, safety, and maintainability.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Data Security Tactics: Protecting Models and Signals</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-security-tactics-protecting-models-and-signals/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-data-security-tactics-protecting-models-and-signals/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Practical AI data security tactics to protect training signals, model artifacts, and SOC analytics. Learn controls for privacy, integrity, governance, and resilient operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Business Services: What SMBs Can Outsource First</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-services-what-smbs-can-outsource-first/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-business-services-what-smbs-can-outsource-first/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Discover nine AI business services SMBs can outsource first. See concrete examples, selection tips, and tradeoffs to cut cost while protecting quality.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in FP&amp;A: 12 High-Impact Opportunities to Pursue</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-fpa-12-high-impact-opportunities-to-pursue/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-in-fpa-12-high-impact-opportunities-to-pursue/</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 04:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Explore twelve practical AI opportunities for FP&amp;A that raise forecast accuracy, speed decisions, and strengthen controls. Learn where to start, what to measure, and tradeoffs to consider.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Convenience Store: Speed, Selection, and Trust</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-convenience-store-speed-selection-and-trust/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/ai-convenience-store-speed-selection-and-trust/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Learn how AI convenience stores balance rapid checkout, curated selection, and shopper trust using data, sensors, and design choices that reduce friction and increase confidence.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street Light Automation System: From Pilot to Rollout</title>
      <link>https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-light-automation-system-from-pilot-to-rollout/</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://pulsegeek.com/articles/street-light-automation-system-from-pilot-to-rollout/</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <description>Plan, configure, and scale a street light automation system from a small pilot to citywide rollout with steps, checks, and fixes.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>